[
    {
        "question": "問題文: 409.9806797854833は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.61276339120692
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.636242860988894は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.803704530608297
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 205.199168406957は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3121755964154045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 123.05830788932512は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.090110939035926
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.026957365966375は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.756080200720266
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 146.3909904331257は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.165514349088621
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.56396346035501は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8485829664069122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.778104493406013は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4437485769149716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 342.8819507128487は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5351446244788316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 979.022723608591は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9907927721129335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.789474730003312は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4455224314679047
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 116.49367996539056は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.066302364584274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.326763528356864は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3667522476837054
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 745.0337252049662は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.872175932263608
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 189.46774652300783は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2775352897696566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.19485494786606は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.305240738141432
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.7163937012727は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5405346048402309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5228001168004528は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18264290145319784
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.350852306337256は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37122534517870553
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.115488536145469は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04746511140663645
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.14132052350659は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0469366685831338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.859006504994538は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8953676482442949
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 730.1598879987948は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8634179709044836
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 108.67011179908178は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.036110113860058
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 773.587598521385は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.888509498902116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 104.91791030675175は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.020849631982322
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8540530079365942は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26812214659664835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.32425875910629は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5719911916140374
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.6327811311911535は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8216956666660508
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.82888382545357は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1697592977966687
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 105.15968506132955は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.021849276784539
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 644.3490597019695は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8091211990891876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.45614691886745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5496915382926764
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.91077460525057は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9026053404670007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 170.2396107224046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.23106061753868
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.375578941372698は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37576946676234635
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.292249466464727は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6326849553164117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.096863613016375は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8510664590708558
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1221436809766536は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.050048468203795604
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.79261425120737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.016166450775766
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.71353424369356は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6406159206622362
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6329637239722654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42044487559402877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 415.14185283452525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6181965193067755
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0969910659558906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04020309063591676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 81.77698729024054は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9126311068624238
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.021640282986053は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6044032223769064
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8559775044632816は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4557547823317487
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7380397207706584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24005969749492195
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 558.5580106076466は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7470682846646395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.868984397274982は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3956580498591837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 275.63693250185645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.440337408109108
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4619262033305773は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16492545039529338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 238.05801437564116は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3766828068587458
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3361960522859728は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12587018432162522
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.79595093285007は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.553833904102752
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 379.7795699503807は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5795315983776694
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 217.69691246612268は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3378522696086903
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 770.7005473985357は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.886885667448548
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 156.47453117115026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1944436589945466
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.02326895505874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5443566792370622
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4006394334645975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38032693564392905
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 309.1908636831815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4902266524176913
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1181338833457422は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.048493808306270925
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.748724043881166は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43913114135842224
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9552316779937127は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.597171927410783
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.21606071738841は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.54674077399403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 347.70872371456846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5412155868971533
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0108860765769037は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47869432334735895
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.00955298789949は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.79940639858708
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.271721055398416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6306028853930397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 244.45211453709754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3881937983101076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7303622039564734は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23813702030504624
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.165147815972252は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7130827546538007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.341603480747519は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.637650156753849
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 641.2095661585394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.806999992937996
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.151005850723623は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33264159166757834
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.946451661534464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.951650819743256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 174.5118234530302は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.241824856432486
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.723595169744414は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0690608132991821
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.988977380899481は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8444136349270457
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.524189484131963は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3715146689267987
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.393574801208617は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0167649459613464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.905457873923865は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6803849954499968
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.214152112692826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6247102077103435
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 388.00680249972083は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5888393396720284
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.961559024417664は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9523835695732389
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 127.84067786537263は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1066690647891457
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 99.13136134602688は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9962110702760532
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2591755601638495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35394998118501075
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 383.2052314398577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5834314293468883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.457537676438267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0954322093204771
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 443.6061913911538は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6469975989474763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 352.6644839737433は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5473617250747056
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.18619444654417は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2091447533155177
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.130150245793773は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.053136183821153815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 647.0176228101402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8109161097026565
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.457492991082454は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.266172712178626
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 78.61031989728609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.895479563599763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.254219993116028は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.366501776727913
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 105.03354303006847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0213280155128333
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.610619967711481は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2069930789692217
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.067827221989296は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7830332059965411
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7289193852164804は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43599070640175464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 52.33752450516792は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7188131772421427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 450.94592930513227は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.654124470897475
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.745347968089406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8890409336803027
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 377.36845083992125は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.576765588995675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.843089612124903は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8944871771201282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.1191945055722154は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7092016310333296
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 859.756437320363は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.934375436232633
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.04291650031484は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.323105931879697
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3935239587325037は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3790377790472311
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.001985782172467は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0000862328622757
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 899.9095414245871は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9541988565120287
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.293087260275346は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7237090537010155
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.30957397222055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.974555783005084
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.582043409742221は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1926244099080334
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5160977926729617は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40072751673860285
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.129754548731857は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0464855866791145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.16620312785651は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6643241581026522
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.464901006639218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1658082774389743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.100895478032508は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49148712770822367
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 107.68277486229147は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.032146238297565
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.323902209744895は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6358758632996758
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.498705705216764は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8027648731532202
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 355.6895981333426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5510711647659177
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.432833206319646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9259735104668679
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 235.19547292001414は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.371428958115076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 887.136461272832は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.947990429098313
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.40596499326206は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.97340335807353
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.78453114305292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5656652248808258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 386.09586405588146は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.586695149390615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1516220716393006は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06130997984211328
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 131.89480127475682は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1202276778649294
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.06756108024319は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.906742262171654
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.469253607411886は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9278451377845754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 370.69841757605394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.569020732133004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 239.58137622312205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3794530552953663
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9573744449595645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47090631576194353
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.305326682052879は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.799707592501091
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 58.79690258647666は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7693544480993877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.017886805536397は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3048968005977599
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.409481466112688は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8068228960531375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7736443269415043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24886653413526183
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 650.2107202704691は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8130541255967865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.661479097780267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.066753638181566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.15578795578402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5334643087281132
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 907.5013281395062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.957847269304003
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.872812800610273は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.20065389433769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.19594068842451は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.792107251757724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.925382491781452は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1739254695797345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.515412741911933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8759528367675736
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.022554598926694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7009246665519338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 254.66002589991686は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4059607789111648
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 470.9271790255499は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6729537559772196
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.43931379699706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.185936647602631
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.233125899675933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3661076458591963
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 129.34597972276845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.111752934704274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 338.2800815482191は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.529276426613378
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.737491660061547は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9884470987175091
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5557564666341295は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19194161484222705
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.257066581491493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4662307800485026
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.406606117486082は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6441042330270076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 734.5784683541331は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.866038194344107
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.51677477185737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18092109654050326
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.02541253597273は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7995156970539208
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.0243281863002は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1673892036112337
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 388.00693123212426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5888394837616753
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 830.0873607393289は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9191238011597895
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.26580923727244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8528812210020962
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 142.08586532520766は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.15255087654401
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.923382749269842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4658856798848583
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.208356611106168は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6241125343000268
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0693756995992065は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.029130311006251408
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.481576891213099は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8116806774507626
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 195.32483847164744は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2907574738319854
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.962879520328824は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4717139921077331
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 382.8025347148828は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.58297480478151
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 104.08214703897912は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.017376242407907
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 858.9738448961884は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.933979940094113
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 612.6492028928307は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.787211872794999
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.70257743487053は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4579208972734283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.998324267908222は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.999927217781594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.729395584122071は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4360664845709049
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.731310448277654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9410794301597661
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 259.0221491523158は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4133369024725395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 239.687285868485は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.37964499763981
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.860323238197397は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.993891152087711
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2779813341558566は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10652451068285729
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 825.8922808139282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.916923407007069
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 721.7695300664959は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8583985441085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.253419083600875は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.419185871263706
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.891925363571919は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8971829693396391
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.283250194728403は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1083113388353637
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3957005922572407は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37943254023829276
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 451.373279183119は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6545358457324175
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.911363256258634は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9961333935318609
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 411.578281423621は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.61445244940736
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7215356533961668は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2359160214716397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.829481823111079は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8937330201920078
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 90.99720378008004は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.959028047249232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.494961200097011は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9291613996120982
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.85936611375996は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3776589013228766
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5580729898803125は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40791293210902
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.2871179149611147は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5168152833023241
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.881848330653368は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6885842826224403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9086730368184537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28073153841605014
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.652590464239575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1659144113707542
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 639.5116993261609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8058484939379214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.897067188789792は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4619585674793164
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.80487193714235は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.89100679222325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1121078972877345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.046146924767126896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6340037904298472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21325305963878183
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 502.03357743851757は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7007327649709043
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 644.9388484386283は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8095185378217846
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 743.3105274199578は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.871170283708398
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 783.3063088992865は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8939316244477684
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.31746509833108は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11973911891077516
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 384.11931863118684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.584466149820576
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.19689930147964は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4799623507256223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 218.16380923085134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3387827079620678
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.171285502031241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7135985154425271
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.33925658800173は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7733421011019717
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 874.8563200659255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9419367335637343
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.903397769138552は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0375618559628204
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.11524250872916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6244393057968707
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.954017761459914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1747578921391648
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0347267890611076は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014825693110254723
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 205.65133151928114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.313131525756715
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 633.5479973246646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.801779522429602
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 584.9082482595167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.767087745740713
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 765.9728528109445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.884213377878911
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.29006765592651は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3671707501299093
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.76987004859433は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5535173623664447
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.16772163577044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0072236479212775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.04330191332835は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9733278690446032
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.205398466084079は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9640425921747559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 527.2569001252315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7220222719899096
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 148.98288480653972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.173136379412176
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5732253440822657は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1967909341186007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.043478462054495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4156989897266277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.725148266758407は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4353901358542488
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 560.7217324381629は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.748747388798808
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 150.7239619776719は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1781823016007738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2037309612960416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08052943120676781
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.064487163157913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8490806403113222
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.109519058090235は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3821885470634425
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 134.32937560375257は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1281709960459763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.15154570166901は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9614944528655419
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 755.5762920017471は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8782783224441433
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.803474617717659は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7636880893353366
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4282605364273673は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15480743658022256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.584259848996939は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41233618010930373
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.429869362962962は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1552963608664787
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.00674363528153は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2306211650756145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 488.9214305377447は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.689239073795451
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 60.99561114135093は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.785298587049039
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0200414943601313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008617838825736968
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.266322580041546は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.665264981525724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 95.16627241826917は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9784830587001219
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 329.3777118978985は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.517694208290798
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.38505361616475は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.951264904984999
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.833385521882242は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4121813251482962
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7176584711601035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43419487792622136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.01691114531348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9040070701617021
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 453.19946072379196は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6562893844110844
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5392269799966565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4047015239355918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 86.3388830008585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9362064257228266
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 592.5074499566697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.772693815365232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 317.82010349884337は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5021813647482554
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.581919356842416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3134858722348377
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 586.1208197239591は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.767987148323504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.634864277642411は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5604881993569811
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.556582904654173は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1919142077803797
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5855349509935044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20017581990855948
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8878993209531558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2759788302584768
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.75349900606719は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5533185503235927
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.46120528228806は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6670904719441397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.365988635165044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1573355185300338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.628197929237178は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9835450095934329
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.831823716692614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45206621467785657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 472.87500942406115は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6747463629559793
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.2294249050358013は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5091251901927613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.486405871377633は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9287237985223371
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.118506636487584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04863856525999444
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.24128924572292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8878495140409468
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7573010615667115は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24484617138515086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7496201701246834は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2429437767301731
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.992841779158024は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9996890110991629
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 86.33579111264282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.936190872892074
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.0070544951122は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6532805912904518
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.24964077552612は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5471546955117663
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.7712563939012は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.169589965834729
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 197.30005467173802は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.295127205594973
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 373.9513622309729は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.572815119611379
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.680917084336813は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2255462912484476
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 76.65217152424019は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.884524462747291
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 812.5725569843103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9098621508090763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.21585963182362は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6254756371377572
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.033719841760906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2795236726210883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.436859657354205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5847478980081013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.57435176369809は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8233069463942009
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3610551138990155は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5264756340005609
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.589210983450847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9817828741539179
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 80.82573462456548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9075496606011955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 667.3761112708313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8243706570251907
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 556.9022980193353は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745779009980004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 431.85874426575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6353417176072993
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.815031217671467は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8929307171773909
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 290.16123676208576は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.462639393681437
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.4648949784857335は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6498112480396747
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.83757193002853は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6418464914938098
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.20123239006626は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.749745838955842
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.1227856163109236は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6151907521979464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.070369038201499は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7050395698701891
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.494128224325624は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7398987909540797
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.245187694084949は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.095234819995211
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.176359985509439は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.151564732882091
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.15464383850806は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8545880192529514
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.643114170901098は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.066069156117174
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.543084219419182は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.470455832531594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6738071131919923は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5651163506972252
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 76.8510641509476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.885649885520666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.408333308407993は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3504095556926003
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7502862512024173は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24310908134419917
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 140.0259783884791は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.146208615850567
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.822648136785105は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7545214695205669
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.049635970211321は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0433479704435116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 249.37311774786988は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.396849635016593
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.247205496726842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6281032743967169
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 269.7711405399248は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4309954880540494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.636276183641115は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8037047580233603
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.780148648995436は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4440680173974104
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.264118302339584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6298292451133946
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 275.2867138442236は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.439785251555414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.417446773453406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5730741495447678
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.555569827172171は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0988364276965497
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 653.1857704073377は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8150367151018534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.100551220379055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04161025971111543
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7025000425808763は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43176570946813775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 408.7468922750957は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.611454463716274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.342273063881596は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.213312462872267
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.955587723938521は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1447481310352283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.397038355085726は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5105053100574333
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.55287069705356は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5508746733514402
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.1761751973034は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8207016625109325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9357876858891103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46772464450667717
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5500552556921434は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1903471799860753
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 325.78304026052706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.512928471890898
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.96581054503991は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.844885869744018
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.399996998342709は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14612710453209832
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 112.77574673810103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0522157114351263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.01496708527276は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8574227665288714
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 270.1909670842218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4316708257701998
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.167814467141404は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7133069133958735
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9162356516773142は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5928688167225015
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.94542404286189は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.016805375277134
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 528.6022407388609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.723128999768942
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.685546236147079は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6707602277779263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.979705686504694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5795515949659749
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1838726115952034は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07330497345305198
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.41670753158263は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.63765688602117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 101.84253127690877は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.007929185087192
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 186.23685931149456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.270065639112469
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.50648844847417は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4984000016368872
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 82.38767577174396は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9158622512040422
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 81.29103273540552は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9100426409406617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.82306538431302は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2509824003182684
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.494208771430366は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5433488495798017
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.76503116911444は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44170003130006985
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.494044779227073は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6526373954694771
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 150.80507339245884は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.178415952338042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 249.24998678159255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3966351439518716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.87043726426192は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.142090152382783
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.73038292806665は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.514951086352107
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.195949486298563は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4799486901846715
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.9544974377224は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.891841176048799
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 905.497117884445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9568870723321603
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 976.0503658933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.989472228594118
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 267.9756096170986は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4280952675707828
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 292.428873359046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.466020251054062
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.392676378234444は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1873141386906807
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 407.91085016213947は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6105652574202427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 254.10156013418373は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4050073315422504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 50.45472190478951は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7029018167816883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.507125629136121は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9780492328055239
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4106514083164425は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1494197067745201
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.944966594851077は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28891214664042597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.291867503724006は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2378418991596716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 131.86909792456987は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1201430353249773
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.532706115116575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6078055998342067
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.035174537022247は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3017931301545673
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 963.4931963682703は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9838486522658365
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 227.2218768194932は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3564501427282316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1445440196803258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.058632500493848716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5218784489417836は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18237996711136095
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.948646744063648は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9517573642520283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.216548070984064は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.450503882365855
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 690.8283482461034は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.839370150601051
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.274690171547628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10540463721022286
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 485.560462238804は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6862433161837815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.9845894892663685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6976293973743559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.352123462105632は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3714601139619057
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0446561089919375は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01897334829703834
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 306.10104714449085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4858648152827194
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.807822360696019は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25715575381650657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.179828123782684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7721736995032025
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.38600649380689は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4967360602672004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.58019152460194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.291816935560631
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 208.6497277974786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.319417822471499
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.650198955524793は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2467496051799078
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 590.0214975884044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7708678355640615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.658830364707384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5398139024423956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.207481279134439は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6240221922921402
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.917590869248265は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5901459481283058
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.985323865287883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0408128651558508
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 729.8402920405465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.863227835635707
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.788064363787498は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7625333518668902
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.89351380613248は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5785648785887594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 52.80318813871237は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7226601450574908
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4971085740084655は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5437091159697455
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.99333101892593は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4312564804763377
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.507623034656865は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17829276432276864
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 623.4604149122005は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.794808884228428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 725.4899597462078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.860631406495338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 178.07884979500787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2506123419069946
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.96334543502576は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1582519302779684
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 363.7430421342573は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5607946946631084
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.21021440352726は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0871075060186337
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.095884752100056は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6123477281847782
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1822959839018794は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0727262143486801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 84.57728746626707は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.927253752490678
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2434925482023336は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35092463135517216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.4825159011619は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8161253570716263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 427.9605999356599は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6314037876622947
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4714243269037848は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3929473172401494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 755.4452713481763は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8782030071099562
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 208.65400802843865は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.319426731477231
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.058050261103084は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.519277235629432
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.114376307318526は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.344674695452873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.18076628510121は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.048471569381048
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.60587693899342は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9474625281797127
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 152.54832511074883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1834074437112823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1554806584240949は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06276268022621445
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.44903360217867は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8416662068171732
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.25265665429775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5938690555081978
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.145279328459899は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05891142205930455
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4364041632274986は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15727665520097878
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.054397044448525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2799952105518
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.4866619537566は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8602581007393653
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.78703004981564は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8181402806502502
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 266.4026073305483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4255384710377843
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 505.1336573838506は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7034063068000025
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.93308447525841は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.868838825264751
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4228205245672267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5343841275242104
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.67074495848035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.938056412061972
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.119824985374614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7867390023787503
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 403.0298552812857は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6053372186067794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.87185564521548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8800807060045208
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.63783898073401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5395507890029734
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.130913519043441は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6160461030871254
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0347912615729085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3085198638822504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 291.5181845936985は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4646656507669915
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.408567672165914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1586208105855305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.2836139797413は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9677170738397131
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5023766218705907は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17677881702028286
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.119830688547376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0051732465309833
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.32670136723739は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9509812967733429
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 173.82433862868842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.240110585645989
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 404.65238966672206は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6070821094536583
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1023560292090675は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.042321881765366665
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.971004197596489は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4729032653989871
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 768.3422203498916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.885554698294418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.33148026686202は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8883563234533238
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.038041971808195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3431730058506062
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.978639874616025は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2782650850082993
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 387.92582934490963は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5887486972811784
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.342422242777474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.496132557098154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.4167067496855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3505718105117348
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.22472892190034は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.821020189272571
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.463243491784735は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3915073439997898
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.18282698056601は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2829126096954067
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.768785962694574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6784078304425293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.9767271266197は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.652987849441904
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7222098646128585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5708008557570969
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 432.9070885839232は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6363946971730035
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.99473765144585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5314116939299256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.03941695468078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0806054554022002
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5301564766768372は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18473584485843242
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.14050737417874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1186121342916477
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.85548225532914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5031841841863214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 534.3641511328054は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7278373149475965
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.137361174265052は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2818820532702984
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.108464113009745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3445585729534977
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 316.31758755838604は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5001233397728466
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 944.8123407079132は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9753455571989678
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3129759198971023は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5202182792584109
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.48594933133479は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0206077548487258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.212306665782983は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.858074184554224
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 78.35712783094448は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8940785086137573
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.943056709917667は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8415507125277227
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.713444156310958は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6733383660372216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 281.78164550190155は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4499127009207835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.738934965306798は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6756807487073788
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.162210591345081は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.006988190545882
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.74911560328435は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8793775666679982
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.8388011781913445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6847377777217011
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 201.86670890437256は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3050647026422384
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.63666834868162は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5395361111926116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 182.51861804837495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2613071718240665
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.012038414330805は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6033650826365226
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3023006059346978は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5188166042255283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.599733368582193は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4248772833553596
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.100142565506815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.43297157556998
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 105.36502969414107は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0226964938849528
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.8354304169973625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6844351380688881
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 215.2573627759815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3329580152164855
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 369.71943472000515は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5678722803535026
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.376711641725379は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6411479341998544
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 64.05612715412052は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8065606775928766
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.466946050059603は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.160376861900748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 196.07395978529897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2924199196622226
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 287.99595286301235は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4593863847675257
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 219.58592307695628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.341604495495928
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2491685898418259は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09662105542537758
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.48365444593488は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5852763063581086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.746317505702555は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0699017357467615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.505410255916203は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0970979438840316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 980.2114156232428は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.99131975603553
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 112.16832589283892は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.049870238096867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 165.5488123244507は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2189260693962263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 343.4220049542748は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5358281193748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 82.65054393633554は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9172457160777228
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.692447764747124は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.067905438402414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 819.0138492563742は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9132912456001847
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6652452034345846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22147819139066383
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0445726854952289は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.018938665294012114
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5596341705517314は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19302274172464984
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.282919680980517は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7981615078569684
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.85152849662187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3394818209142756
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 521.3991134328231は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.717170288375156
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0425084191293514は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3101638553507855
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8526421971561513は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45524730213531983
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 693.6679318675654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8411516176148877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1278011218646697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32793103353229214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.848221594962304は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5030851863398742
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0660606663577337は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4865807437354934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 260.5400983539447は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.415874572755299
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.39215670316415は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6473062448570954
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.643933046546934は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4255983336489955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5650635096497754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19453196573601772
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.510357996227135は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2674148182279177
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.4885554090963575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7394580529357164
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8397252342347385は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2647529653104993
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.791723035997087は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6804917076670813
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.357502079597093は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3724520845088968
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.74791279998376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4432303210247923
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9101884078847085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5921976838749806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.5631251911804456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5518310816503956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 93.29663275800887は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9698659695663765
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7951633732251555は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25410397874246815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 128.71018137582882は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.109612902308041
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.670288403833155は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7609521232832765
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 688.3738888805661は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.83782438848563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 414.0091487509371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6170099382420284
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 187.86500017940674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.273845877254396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.26182362095694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5827656653683457
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.32994263754429は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9606131848765762
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.637031425597953は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6662400391603148
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2623170847745524は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10116846019400727
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0169690825478668は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30469924110727875
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 785.7883865819227は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8953056059460627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 262.11766788744177は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4184962952976794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.48825229886728は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.266895859086058
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.07293853374168は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7833988855039395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.61741887061172は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4251659390199598
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.65407522578916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5521091764578125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.922783522163982は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9505003565890349
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.25330650714633は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6258607000696161
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 404.8340604802547は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.607277044484752
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.47352789316459は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1895893421324573
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.175406009229859は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7139444257524381
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.90056636677674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.902549857775745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.794080580293137は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4884672418776086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.0205514508351は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6629518183878145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 528.0243258615486は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.722653930761239
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.825615079765406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5661500093780005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 191.7817319695018は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.282807236397271
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 182.0183203007099は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.260115102298713
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 658.0035211459825は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8182282176415825
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 562.3838696641008は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7500328557238323
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.576102610758085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1327751118020775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.070845842574632は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7050804078784132
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.26290741266393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.051650513986817
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.692243396863493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2716614274574818
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 221.91026071517038は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.346177383660376
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 641.139030367554は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8069522160621676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2509319149502727は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09723367279009154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.34786016205161は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.548363128233583
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6688153414071274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22240828356677667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 962.8040556574297は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.98353791100259
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 239.9607914493456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3801402856771388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 248.48107917104392は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.39529332456048
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.504004834986796は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.190443895143207
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.271961270771107は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35640092385510946
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.847805038960998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4545102541355932
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.01648971757271は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.007102989836803353
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.11350511050959は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6142120411984879
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 615.1238831077775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7889625894860397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.97447358233911は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6967471288241348
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 393.3296279295338は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5947566612881494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.50519670662258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8293372071145404
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.845589038870868は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6853465782457848
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 302.4536214287144は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4806587888998797
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3955209892661289は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1447363728589801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3729669468474979は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13766008204773084
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.371117763494は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6845861232145602
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 845.7553153468609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9272447358937246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6165093013577176は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5582895864034477
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.42559067878924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0943170430746907
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 96.69057041191465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.985384122296494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.41238929218117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0175503968829909
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.049044844072403は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1155787236183479
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 257.2544184979476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.410362842765073
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 82.01541224705585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9138954721995387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.51474405957613は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6768283942591786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 438.9392783953313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6424044453405173
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.666664903714658は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2471545715429926
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 134.47109150950786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1286289300833
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 176.4494918912784は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.246620412091671
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1889560350709427は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5036485318306967
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4333347153259592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15634761959816745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 41.94801717356765は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6227114371330131
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.51927483902908は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.978603865884119
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.979267203199946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5438107070025726
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.177569467710511は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7141259345555341
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.712422812156574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7568203448099067
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.949132704400006は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1122406815982102
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.57835876732128は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2690073452992392
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.413604153424133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1587725906841402
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.216184892178462は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7935239234985637
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 620.4698103235725は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7927206552483694
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 160.01274591010167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.204154578018126
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.238353245628915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8009805521892024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 54.23707445553253は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7342962556730777
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.31658653350029は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1558394826101572
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 880.2967240288616は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.944629085658578
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.127054462189039は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7098679307625265
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 109.65613243029111は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0400329242594495
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 106.73982056389198は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.028326468392835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.38661231514614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5488389880893285
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.320494151443495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12073648202803022
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 416.5678053408127は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6196857022341
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.447732254514365は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9267401407212638
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 133.21601056350346は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.124556423644522
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.023790585221238は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.010211131460305056
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.63580738672693は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4414721571203686
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 328.6056397951829は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5166750128753916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 280.3955622800298は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4477711359260534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 254.45141314326963は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.405604867151227
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.918273277526396は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0381539602242427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.055449765145656は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6080390261646972
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 121.84312445761753は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.085801027206712
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 86.67086264944587は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.937873119190255
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.56776178807311は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.08837625551139
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 344.3473122262393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5369966974857983
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 320.65292456132283は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.506035205316886
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.52381838693972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8604806616772214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.0242827343099625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6046884853771775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.566821077733778は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0992254317828731
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.463596124719633は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2892230842794494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.6188685251075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6645356003428954
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.636172031909502は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8219176358726064
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 949.562901398565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.977523738768122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.06999545023787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5918433606505151
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.55410113922805は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.608034779930009
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.94570805730979は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.530784871846039
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6404379656291708は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21495981186663615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 401.8782251463311は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6040944755750086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.352774380036811は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.156935857967591
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 294.4778561113282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.469052642653738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 68.92679361519305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8383880761495326
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.035149835391342は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.080451501530748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.98049571776897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.819415574117523
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 108.63899515633244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.035985739999035
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 958.8610861291121は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9817556938260754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.555217601851291は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5508661874542826
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 474.6618658640461は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6763843420826556
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.78067363461334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.901897698990119
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 221.5826818923401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3455358144837413
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.062143509934943は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.314318885682752
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 290.617701084651は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4633220629876957
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 138.8674091199524は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1426003328496
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 965.7495983528712は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.984864536197476
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 573.8129871926042は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7587703734712457
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.69203963995875は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6502301752950834
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.293052076451475は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8629093146784191
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2208924470119136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08667740700254623
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1857481526878684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.503211439945606
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 729.9006423372292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8632637458444683
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 241.3011500615は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.382559391797609
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 643.6936306919072は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8086792118335775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 272.798921617988は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.435842649209211
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.018377738944806は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6040507592485934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 62.73731136404775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7975259028733959
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.212909460274947は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5068984873140423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5576690511987414は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4078443483769282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 139.7131165268886は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1452371804008328
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.604642894485659は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6631959548438309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.834420407421234は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.566253840585933
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 409.96088398259366は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.612742420912593
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.212313942082442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9144655433176395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.707841302845935は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4872492875204428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.38601053369124は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2144732297082
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.432333684465913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2156992453775242
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 543.9872394631343は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7355887123898253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.64107433110302は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.425551734261854
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 180.89389971087627は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2574239213839955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.01073829462347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3804055141741194
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 504.75221301758546は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.703078231725075
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4393358576060504は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.158162144934467
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0091830863941733は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30301951354654155
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 378.1468142910119は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.577660446020869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.082718084287127は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7060960219919332
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.984360832007535は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9534871858405414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.463748117359048は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7374906698531026
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.87030414203682は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.254959469005415
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 428.64390629985826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.632096654076617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.916212845331223は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.276834192054786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.055756667674146は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3022390517774702
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.34464331669855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8995176121680428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.793490815785571は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0331619263185434
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2772371748657754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10627155049073655
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1103935065397375は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04547691341138649
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7873047970267066は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25219862098868473
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 110.25229770461071は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.042387649115253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.578113937433464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0996155244181705
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.526335797364241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7424372704667657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 501.6533488968744は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7004037158200895
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 60.44889225306276は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7813883466725522
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.266020618452536は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3276862306110808
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.335147526836455は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8017567327703675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 171.36436743807158は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2339205221740768
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.036489509260488は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3985734342174299
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.2297899337518174は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5091742766409527
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.45722815321197は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0590795614908515
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 275.7407116527744は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4405008921153613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.293582807342949は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6328198432508824
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.942526135406116は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9514602180909062
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.305111658194363は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3284838146411704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.88997011389108は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5170634788527342
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 568.0937659176361は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7544200234923166
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 448.7411756176483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6519959213785924
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.603002406279963は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3139305132558838
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.049828681526696は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9566403578381489
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.466279326375292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6499458808737819
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5478321147804848は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40617080748333956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 803.7205653543315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9051050810635144
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 708.7732017170694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8505072887796463
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 269.5915962946167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4307063502529007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.640925110468435は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9841187093275937
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.783645510351027は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.106654719179477
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.365879071040574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.308903160676008
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 58.3384093105014は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7659545832174959
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.662059534093819は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5637254003475085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.8623825178993325は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5868552826972276
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8881262291098553は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4606161706870223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.314437362789502は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8641809251799243
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.62129273665056は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4252291410996676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.385366435460288は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4045834367872962
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.944466470829943は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.774112881802083
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 281.3203010220348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4492010734510896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.48826898178386は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9771869879561725
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.921759825417478は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7724507893060524
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0136628557805696は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47909466534293477
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 287.59952394872545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4587881628422332
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.66757580789272は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0028896104219402
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 515.2030807932217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7119784513383545
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.142618321635872は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4004105026031994
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.88241902550442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1699165460452106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.50380774519577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.585503680182676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.51927292350597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3714238918007835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.146895108107538は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8541174081954194
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 823.5928187683606は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9157125511770876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.377742072478883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9720982836342656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 605.4997884279026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.782113995729095
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 722.9184389759068は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8590893021343824
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.060752388796878は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1778466684211675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.44253077356334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.595964773047359
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.550005158943202は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1903331436521215
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.613766128068866は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8815995324666465
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2498776339182744は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35215889839616044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.082049379719619は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.034247080410484076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8918540789983689は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2768876356969867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 58.75237458656707は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7690254241182803
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.934962268896946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.202351039480335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.86160979800209は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8316241576683232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 455.35189986141336は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.658347152919344
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 180.1085760180629は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.255534392601027
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.023055563376257は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30600781086587303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 142.05096629756179は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1524441923445696
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.08201880838643は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4925092189084292
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.265270410367426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.122716107430556
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 127.55934283160086は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.105712273150534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.171074150134537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6202479104663109
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4882475182085428は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17267516699786534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.632715040634732は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0266441748346058
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.74776825983407は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.855808396729889
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 984.259571457542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.993109646790672
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.973576156090948は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9988509081993603
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.49307428193501は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3520488174825167
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 220.9973213857119は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.344387009818801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.68632440541204は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2941646374454772
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 230.1459065488459は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3620032547935037
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.814708593907335は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8334472895523721
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 425.3747976856092は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6287717555471937
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.39798969728977は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8286469428796157
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.87966951038761は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.016530559266436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 402.7123520480338は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6049949505511396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 759.7280265156465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8806581479082736
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.428144911625875は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4220666794798151
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8327635805366087は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.26310644625492585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.853443805192203は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4601976558395116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2460957955188845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3514282748898381
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 564.248150779026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7514701444307375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 657.8969705172453は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8181578865633616
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.80828583231008は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.254809700791743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.648938097230922は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8836011461962092
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.92096906685371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6805255918547894
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9138794356652182は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5926074433884706
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 108.14978440485717は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.034025658015756
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.249787339144333は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4807223258393711
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.471956180440273は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3516408793346955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.042258762105362は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2315271551552833
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9053318321235313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.463195742450941
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 244.6544839117583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3885531797129156
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.99039833524379は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6720091265310406
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.944872067832673は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4763224620068693
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.19578233259545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1817230640068122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 834.6954549550371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9215280487075184
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 610.703358896761は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.785830308642201
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 644.8872405600628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.80948378427309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7970894916261322は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2545697046836374
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 166.89944212201775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2224548850091796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.174314334417367は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3258093559283513
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.463850235525133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1893176349806636
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.147910765450936は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9110462640340093
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.4103879189109225は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8068843112574913
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.28757697471672は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4359649738073492
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 475.42500123613974は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6770820162928732
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0541618325386186は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02290728790062313
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.907059525213474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7713713472487563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.629876274271442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2702099706461294
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.825878105744028は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8341585285257703
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 80.5601628390286は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9061203354008258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 84.25540419010859は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9255977663347403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.535691911982995は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8771231345219711
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.49661826392217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9003486544356458
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 64.51813950991834は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8096818352788269
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0700669759414378は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02941096120995279
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0985412669369021は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.040816375927767656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.502317553475878は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0969905255994847
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2342470451994965は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09140209618722206
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7869022386015776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2521007929100795
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 508.12861594718316は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7059736534775203
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.2555358636274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7727289299178919
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3338933893454508は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5229517079217201
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.12282570430761は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.624517497048728
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 149.9764566622862は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1760230887613226
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.1079633444247は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4640118193439549
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 563.2481608091167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7506997822835633
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 194.06275770756432は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.287942198582723
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 382.6717463995665は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.582826398373631
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.40828067670462は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5612001705502525
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.734917516038273は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.501537373852875
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.496610720646125は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6674212969981905
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.326400646459808は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0540919197723437
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 86.90610097826243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9390502658409232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.069806439624257は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31592973379819045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 220.38246084855405は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3431770282024873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 456.4156938141102は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.659360569181075
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 409.0516571334904は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6117781563970737
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.940941446302862は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.253845228797628
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.583604646116736は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3135214316914647
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 51.489182338764174は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7117159951758003
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.525381450095452は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18337846070342978
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.26700599041558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.604949339312408
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 146.01474587548577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1643967169417944
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 245.06123576434328は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3892746191873138
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.53092222680087は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5382081773260619
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.7835979962112は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9904985994233635
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.469141193506402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2664467014179004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.28947841881624は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0526738777033051
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 118.72757933581704は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.074551613327918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.006746067490528は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3024924205867263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.50639645441946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9297456198492388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 450.24387907055376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.65344781742949
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 446.09183394651075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.649424273220479
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.4856208092005は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9286836208608074
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.930974897787097は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.11163126863667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5900044054625966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20139832763205234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.169815514309029は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1809802992043463
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 511.9077270477917は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.709191685105803
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 246.15915962469626は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3912160005818617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 239.74976543796495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3797581909457364
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.938130022237277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8997182081359865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.386993647860654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1579700518552396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4577198246013783は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.390532372624931
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.58934090383527は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.499540564657491
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4718051176579443は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1678503086910902
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.258802240234201は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7208868392694565
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 41.933635083482464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6225625115395044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.970025598225966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.689930331038136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.629830901256147は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8825149128611517
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.365075094895882は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9224698440614154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 58.415369044051936は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7665271247304393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 904.7770447025636は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9565415734763363
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2043695390046134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08075976277437902
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.586112991643704は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1639395735117246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9497105927082305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5965652747164613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 109.86969685910307は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.040877926257842
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 185.60906702872848は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2685991877468648
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.740917937655409は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.168524528492219
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 178.9870004358333は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2528214899519767
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.923424932379889は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7725728890090293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 92.37213632195771は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.965540987815878
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.06095407724361は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2320033139883861
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.580737387689641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1925880076257918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.579573341795035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8796447596532722
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 186.23217964415434は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2700547262392337
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.40784984339772は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7738438341803229
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 121.44336936963512は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.084373807944856
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 682.7918992143577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.834288359912858
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7569869539636653は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4404347110332325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.263008764572653は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0516544220697863
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 590.482770239505は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7712072298088444
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 222.33195484302095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.347001886516563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.08804357851324は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.17863292975967
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3372168021843422は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3686989997799869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 376.58416926792773は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.575862059323529
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.22737863396537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6456911994071088
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.304541127854815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3674405559876548
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.4714164534238は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6671859100198776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.836000598464635は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4527063181576655
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 530.498204801672は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7246839185935388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.03906683549722は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0130019168826876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3825645206832373は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14068540784136907
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 533.7872798233834は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.727368220316354
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.094959402782756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6820995624805355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4429098426597329は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15923919591774127
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.81675104005463は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.850135998138796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.53593095596881は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.860553189334646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.698028866590214は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.696339163998137
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.022191759024928は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9553120534202323
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 41.992315842583146は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6231698262912129
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9900270563341067は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29885898110152753
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 643.03026791523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8082314159711603
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 970.9102381853423は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9871790807187657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.38059249924548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8997143361709496
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.44746745179218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8718499285432753
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.8093950334921は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.157787259328647
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.723522840340294は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3931103531932503
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.74816170521547は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2546644575229955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 50.44745565630123は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7028392672569044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0740005098705643は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3168088588196303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.896906405622972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2780459030951733
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.017486161630531は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0420825136923924
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 139.65229204094422は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1450480679465525
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 542.2878677545579は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.734229888362824
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.32836183358313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8769585229301138
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 807.1710477901831は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906965575911631
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.191865322242336は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6550602674749928
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 511.8601660562748は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7091513332324464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.392042276769015は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9238676630455167
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.58348980051623は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5388688155612509
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.67566428035144は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.659684872197388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 96.64809576370055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9851933016396455
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.897602386960678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9492729942410646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.709001317147318は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8869981198739484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 373.4812855176929は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.572268844973308
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0967832155181148は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3215535314805892
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 935.1571850079066は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.970884614983915
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.46837748240016は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.370483065107825
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.010274913023494は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0795529484389303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.73213631181109は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8735073972858767
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 592.3842448391384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.772603499426461
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 819.677272286231は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.913642893293869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5467583292290858は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18942246335600543
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.6415763936818は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8171790021625398
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 52.54990786593942は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.720571958930404
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 680.8739706455424は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.833066731709426
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 294.3218348631122は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.468822482313016
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.025416061371117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01090011563043769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4052034887594576は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5321430696716448
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.73395262213483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0307596740523006
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3632317750311906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3735063173500406
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.482600318449624は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9285290044788387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.54956762017972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1509085470995193
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.706898629994274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.410049685000527
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 109.46578793327365は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0392784074555537
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.42550607907479は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3309310889268033
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 551.5808688634622は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7416091946120122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6675380918384946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42611062976741565
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 95.4240696772897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9796579345526113
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.137696940046972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2078415553180877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.324792022169117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4817978310082216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 428.24838574275674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6316957345929843
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 68.1239456114734は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8332997935428632
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7516265619820364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5742196020572155
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 206.7415584203437は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3154277856668615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.92200620133958は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6119569168488643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 433.6818641163351は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6371712610261304
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.047574517576965は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0808996212129136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 87.85782512845486は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9437804483442627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.471826338014548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3886663820581193
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 136.67349333509526は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.135684295002879
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.500791463037238は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.060727728719009
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1852418740675823は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33949951396511757
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.38315245007384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8154658562667672
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.382408938060895は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1578316329792777
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 116.20397872430026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.065220998178466
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 713.7752647860931は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8535614938115166
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.96423680262617は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.476603220573164
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 686.0600845442281は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.836362152504581
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 969.62364335721は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9866031968122884
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.93870001426581は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5555623636232108
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7821887714264832は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44438659352358634
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.183168204023193は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4499898126265776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 133.08794603120938は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1241387225731487
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.973166040174631は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.473219163600509
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.059373095142015は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31373503456499585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.443506712671493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.405576967078938
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.66868143073067は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8553294143394237
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.003859814892525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6024788633416424
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.412995729130834は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9249506684454594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1397680963654313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05681649632410579
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.541974372415144は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3126421830702597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.289243425063155は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6363799956262428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.4987955433668665は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7402675720116995
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.94163410192456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.868889044203097
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.890663287369733は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8971135114397165
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 183.01120810546595は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2624776879233273
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 650.8349985160137は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8134708989877666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.52157882583689は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6286093815008154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.854335338209426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.686129774159811
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.6580425605634925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6682034523681397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.72433479519697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2724063978050475
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.313853077110092は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0134209405034256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.176965886093401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7907752028396684
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.971439459773936は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1452411532316806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.410050606453234は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8698211739750554
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.435324408919826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6067609317656306
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.976095587883697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2958079484936983
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.24236214983405は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0138579324942887
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 136.27175165035445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.134405838418389
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.6543912182588905は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8839106553785591
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.92242442543564は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5304868835894476
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 148.9589465325583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1730665922307515
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 280.17008235859464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4474217577867505
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 578.8237914592347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.762546373668683
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.059391344505784は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5688982822820368
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.252300319835438は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0108213194530005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6860689381763416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4291171546787036
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 120.87792703177135は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0823470035614258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 208.14573643904305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3183675194266837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 61.19964238981041は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7867488844235715
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.071865938901377は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0817744038451798
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 524.4194776348579は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.719678813590601
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.21567639471423は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1822912631656042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 464.3681135961868は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6668623907291957
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 377.3736978440464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.576771627468396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 123.07230516737664は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.090160335090732
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 722.997907079062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8591370401087355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 212.8780789961768は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.328130942503853
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 64.22678526602435は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.807716184879331
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.64345335337916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5137960965580282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 653.4784700649521は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.815231283598252
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 557.5482562222966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7462824618620725
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6518763481031258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21797753490545468
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.019261340296026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3620913835431059
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 481.6076168640118は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6826933468873326
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.259064268200537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7965094109208561
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 961.9135615370732は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.98313604767804
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.251608742329753は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8604343638692626
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.8582768243124965は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5863933842613055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.644630560128597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.165678420215548
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1883876919486114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34012426352919667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.984957904086704は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47493821079142895
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.443010169529114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.468982208966633
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 156.36277763678962は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1941333766592623
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 187.47568995652847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2729449605852494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.49894827678709は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39775726719550886
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.451737437703738は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7365349315165841
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 246.91547790726503は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.392548314553353
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.215145603079755は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7260352547709612
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.063670395551444は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31464033402880354
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0971791101102348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04027753020279867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 131.62285581618644は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.119331309437355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.5280925201880784は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5475399654848082
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.093795571280011は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03893616060696248
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 182.85607163992958は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.262109385433915
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 308.1063743719611は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4887006834708876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.318347216295544は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9693388889101989
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 307.8135708815012は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.488287763088139
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 172.9676242430126は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2379648203054163
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 132.51942246517535は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1222795345089414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.372828583812464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8676341367961186
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.407707841125904は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7330132202090397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 732.2970798107442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.864687302299341
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 84.43087617113687は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9265012961347099
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 301.5328060734984は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4793345692841893
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 162.0186742275558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2095650740894124
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.547502958305299は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8778032919204305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.448037044155656は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.128658896746869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.025640458921934は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3983852008053606
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.896428792129406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.652211797182514
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 599.8476075695845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.778040931053836
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.467355645816277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16653538739217755
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 76.18332618521517は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.881859930156769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 169.7184701959544は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.229729108479626
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.334233780750106は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9208656785385553
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.13420758531639は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6824538265893865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3748750518845265は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13826323144427566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6111549074478402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20713729846734852
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 612.5018187950124は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.787107382655288
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 602.7497073769957は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7801370082082024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 295.67535733108053は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4708151303391106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.71941875409769は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1678906607574584
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.36592463859216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.801855776497411
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0688923875934904は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.02893398413596615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 98.35724462920717は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9928063539514693
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1137212561895975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3250477148160291
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.53391311921563は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6564731937334298
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 905.73791431676は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9570025477514994
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.410606782953195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6375958563442643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 232.28928602713347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.366029179121802
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.670155448326724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.472319821685014
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9831044777854は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2973455951586136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.55049505654917は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8296285361787703
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 339.5742020936277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.530934688892414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1605817236056852は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3345706980667077
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.952997354032323は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2907016548956681
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.658135542685706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3739805156330371
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.70029478779716は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2545487895441916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.72047778511001は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.609812865061008
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 54.594161686915164は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.737146201629141
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3524955691584457は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13113585101099945
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.867951339104541は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1420123091023675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.05189082718374は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5321412323431551
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 639.3582518033274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8057442747204955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.31292568945775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6749798043474677
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 347.10521324943466は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5404611364846064
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 211.95106198920334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3262355969594197
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.573634371671247は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1326961465716534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.99468788835048は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3978477180354614
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 459.74026888220925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6625125454892653
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 111.08392127018534は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0456512019743798
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 992.9454252771546は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9969253792584047
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.7212506179794325は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8274500894159987
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.984432757933085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6976157415610768
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 620.1447573979448は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.792493076596901
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 325.3885824696911は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5124023099487056
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.92582519762583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8803895207329153
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 134.41697243133126は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1284541092527234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.436786558738022は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15739225647995814
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.016341222139203は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.007039540637743258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7618038414897725は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44119282935345616
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 213.08489880620078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.328552672625862
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0200394931222618は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008616986774696911
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.653984781836982は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2215181634706371
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1255996331394866は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05138394287949444
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.2094898970785035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7167952001268214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.16518500404629は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3831901243633278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.695729368182953は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2717424127583974
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.935275475930588は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8995620080410743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0548526591591565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31278068674336656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.152693113306144は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6183298376539911
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.95127063623816は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4764152513864754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.345424930872774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7733872438657978
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.493135197921705は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39674583009595654
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0447385630490098は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.01900762553770985
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 885.6174632102743は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.947246171670444
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.085782673053689は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7843164393828476
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.04865953065797は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8695172010921004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.205580778452821は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34352296825538475
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.4020100065138は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1584231083327103
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 556.3881696162227は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7453778870910086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 388.90608847880674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.589844742252759
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 947.0826393091126は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.976387875761539
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 567.2071017714345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7537416598351605
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.159621388405872は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4996350450306417
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.432485098508984は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2655838914758313
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.568969120367353は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8790367334204292
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.830846715663737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9460023464213919
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 302.5292851245887は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.480767421145234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1698427769176134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.33642826675598814
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9098703190081003は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28100387947222316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.556753462435822は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5510537629607559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.24670912604195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7198869878772927
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 867.3306817972158は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9381847098165146
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 82.71254220349378は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.917571369247418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.328472189429281は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7266027034327106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.767577886495864は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5771191335100965
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 457.51957018022983は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6604096755379993
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.085266721072216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1785529932956162
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.379953164948745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7736398507168742
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.95542324132936は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9635773476505334
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.88072129988021は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6007630045474643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4288660800991715は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15499152662203763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.155620862870501は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9616878001042494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.616963539137442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6643564448751743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.13622640919125は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9500542442402278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.483169129041246は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6515851230781115
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 360.96278675691は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.557462430883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 51.00279845968269は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7075940059460715
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.460400627592427は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7372245079006583
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 410.65683300657906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6134790535419112
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 974.9053862369282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.988962469822602
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.537309421723874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5486730508437933
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.476492012950598は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5411412359550686
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2078810226941075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08202415801676433
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.122430587532874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8526282254652751
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.06055010177252は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6085848734739159
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 55.88761398441826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7473155686332502
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 283.5334694664421は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4526043321764837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 300.373704494274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4776619107126594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.03673587653477は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.771122337466788
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.05120756910718は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9058610233825769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.8322947006645665は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8938890200188512
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.2538208453922は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.870718805859641
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.523171498862647は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.131078555727714
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.758437196748204は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7304466349212544
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 826.2274161913716は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9170996018038196
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.89181939815026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1580361039349896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9048969341771413は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46313072821957146
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.8351325674455596は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5837803806226839
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 589.3907714600135は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.77040333148783
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.9182236539469は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.490214534423206
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.431083159128036は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3697923653856625
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1062739444793985は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32351485537679836
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.726655103281661は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8277991606125549
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.340005274087567は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8656963719741502
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.021465296913586は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6043843253265222
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 245.5221605038313は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3900906970707347
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7792626474728537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4439295906630123
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 323.035977984199は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5092508943740115
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 320.1917136870898は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5054100885247625
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 359.7551544304983は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5560070250539138
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.95962463463901は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.077717549078545
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7633819760519276は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44144092061167484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.0133916095408は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8693103058924039
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 87.80087957885877は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.943498866638806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 351.0352376289572は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5453507140147904
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4712703989521188は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16769249732365832
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.845493962634592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8946202925364586
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3691876744988236は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3745994645939812
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.864593946609736は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.141907154885459
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.917055762188406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9502214824807109
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 276.67787491639797は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.441974431327786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.969609080743933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47269928256643234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2789852554799663は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1068655378323683
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.652400602343523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0274474904852464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 168.26253228656213は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.225987420594123
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.924438191637456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0764379268300273
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.70472431217968は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.353540649557325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.5298820658267545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8149053376880627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.036452539146065は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7807817903956159
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.0548189545774775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7037056053402687
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.4025273761939は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4216455016046055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.60257008360618は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.889876104694335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.070982210870085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7248571254061627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.468524035180714は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.561918186775592
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 211.33131065843534は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3249638465023668
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.95726143441043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.579294871120175
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.50820103119737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3326040870542768
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.283082915525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4028300289286935
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.826203094077634は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7545486391455887
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0792865494937571は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03313676474056593
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 979.085858485226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.990820777841317
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.28977549135241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5830828199086007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2286577874666136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08943093763800958
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 156.31230915445755は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.193993178834088
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.20630770389609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6647012659025937
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7510998719478303は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5741586272694715
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.280817998612177は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0892272951807123
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.453379718508376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3107650811366494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 184.40642252053746は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.265776042621387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 120.988648465323は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.082744625356666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0775385480937234は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03243281565405587
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 128.13978985177403は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1076840074169643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.80721260176482は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.868098804100677
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 614.5346122529435は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.788546348552225
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 123.69936497728392は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0923674701418986
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 132.26530657798344は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1214459429203893
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5097754575702775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.178912361339855
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.0289819385152645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7014800758640686
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.61536629348701は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3731946862246576
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.023757372453204は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6436871062883105
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 294.76279215568417は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.469472661747018
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 668.3150798963574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.824981260677618
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.5844878525287545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8799262600957043
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.2637596891569824は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.629792719326654
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.90330003538587は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2765376275622322
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 639.4762967677023は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.805824451279453
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 277.9978024885786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4440413629293847
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 262.2131161246862は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.418654411679416
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.054977511378842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8484956337247195
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 495.4781805948476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.695024534187789
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 741.3534115562437は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.870025290434064
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 768.785501338821は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.885805184301592
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5212946301085717は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40162359885129484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.74400010127984は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9481390004765469
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.771214878212092は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6786289760475772
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.91062035932467は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5552229076686621
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.458442497768697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.422564275432241
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1353458244122385は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.055128167042679865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6311779701905706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5600475349436232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.320400247105724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1852701114348876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.203186830475994は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3430513269303235
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.21953262926542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.870518215208532
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.28265757726987は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3527277607056964
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2494849591135813は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35208309365814805
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.830049024903473は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8344238209829442
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 821.0727632524502は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9143816458877247
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 187.31807183890285は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2725796787169474
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 879.4224637137928は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.944197554918372
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.19491954183815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3653928703837148
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.38368048569707は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6756287911387435
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 816.7169664330938は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9120715776917643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 342.7330570880008は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.534955994766988
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1631904880010913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3350947645824922
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 185.12823896112187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2674726699121788
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 668.7048811055153は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8252344932753513
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.242501265493104は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5937566809500485
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 398.7947013623339は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6007493793678345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.75484347212167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8296152897042453
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.419054564576083は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9740073127723123
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8305315527945907は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2625772191975979
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 140.10638730854998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1464579347834563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.3556219270345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.125664116482462
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.06733162405326は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.799804456402157
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 529.6265991442442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7239697883113307
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.140927692213237は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0842518725890067
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.97411869083838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4620102348504145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 178.64231546734678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.251984339195573
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.510063370019331は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5453149572069296
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 253.8978536368191は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.404659029516394
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 383.19597446951553は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.583420938102595
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0658016534983847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.027676389675457158
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.157624613481338は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7124497297704487
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 50.006808598453254は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6990291390446202
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.9556654506893は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6527844306393724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.2470798040655895は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6280904216075136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.362215690667716は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7293442791326491
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 438.0734442368573は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.641546927291503
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.25711643143915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6744672180132185
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 932.5271341038734は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9696614774996393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.398308424498317は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.453292471603885
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 797.5876310940295は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9017784103621973
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.671505532051384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8242238504804891
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.471909628724828は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8734316105475889
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.255846873702188は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7962861098216028
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6568047582369803は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2192713331530789
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3910649241561566は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3785913685958895
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.961782224670088は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.471553122348221
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 426.25145569033765は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.629665875161144
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 176.57229869632218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2469225708894798
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.038354313898472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0805671213701045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.770921612785943は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6786022810707302
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 218.21803653758428は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3388906438005184
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 438.48449422807556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.641954240369679
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 87.90387241332037は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9440080073910966
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1118545629677175は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32466400634499437
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 797.8129390318497は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9019010754741537
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.170249383058381は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3365096414352581
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 99.82748025049767は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9992501092067063
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.069475511588415は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7564038812493319
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.47643587721367は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2168632725150639
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7529229795226329は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2437628343464121
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.887272795232114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6890665809265738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9262114037048466は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2847039496753707
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.484829192253809は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3952965405900013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.40784587251794は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5611949839777737
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1698723815227532は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06813848822190471
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 432.4547912535324は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6359407131063786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 215.7806919305998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.334012581388838
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.088272790953768は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7844941031829792
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.034131430998622は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0427381526702533
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.73857071610565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6756473662070688
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 347.47092760429496は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5409184736478174
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1673747844858777は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5006994549740345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.67354330235068は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.817390448526748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.249193659305042は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09662977115868898
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.081371823203545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03397504918019767
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.239096670832776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0102616433412102
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 932.5162422975908は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.969656404961996
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 905.513928885373は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9568951351487307
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.8388065433159095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6847382592547535
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.80287722676053は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7308055011365213
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.601762404675021は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9345874424306233
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 332.3754993982065は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5216290028728237
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.0341241385243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.155439660941287
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 611.4195660364275は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7863393324693777
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.281776770344736は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.184173851405657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4949129378165216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17461590053545073
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.04665915589971は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7485497301620372
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 585.9170006477625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.767836099441885
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 619.6208940473826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7921260540459927
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.903685023934581は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5914747685526287
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.281857776376903は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.722786702859869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.07820786174193は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.253042739499375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 204.5239040035583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3107440740555782
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.80466045515724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.688461295636245
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 87.5503580832111は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9422579266986724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.455198971791779は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0193323022449357
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4765919116991426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16926048516591852
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7450786705060244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5734609450816265
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 139.76900208975968は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1454108644419914
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.946757417012678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4693443853276682
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.06479157137706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9497060559089634
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 127.91084196005941は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.106907357644144
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.67083091588955は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3153579345340507
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 468.7276044106335は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6709205308408723
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.54646719293023は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.470505560671164
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 320.96140535716336は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5064528129402897
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6975195769205045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.229814791553141
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.031085367712734は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.343035893319502
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 119.77787673857641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.078376610226793
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.279007459362532は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6313430435667003
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2358798179268806は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09197624021161777
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 282.7339800398162は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4513780067808346
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 238.38898575370249は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.377286185896674
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 359.99255769455027は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5562935224739562
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0761607593885556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.031877152092821937
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.64134011806946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2465315730733617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 125.8895605217199は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0999897174328
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.738451150609858は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6756364077781908
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 700.1579635340386は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8451960328025745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.54462138649924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8165370591381778
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4348681470565279は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15681199470297358
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 127.58627249763101は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.105803949469445
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.18695005948856は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4798192362676779
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.875529004905146は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.688021744433922
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 572.3160720118815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.75763594211329
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 490.32816323325966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6904868387602052
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.19299257156635は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9634569091834925
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 326.2144389753108は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.513503179967656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0777298594871034は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03250991554787519
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.30630755083814は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8882149301766282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.21574930020226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2359259297337672
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.02564643523583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.362211831673009
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 302.19839170472966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4802921487004923
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.33455280856184は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3682037023009256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 93.40785701515614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.970383408508586
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.862586190429997は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1418442593852975
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 278.87056356705244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4454026743410235
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 602.4590222396079は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7799275126237704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 316.17656503284235は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4999296769368136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.86075155555821は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5665641858234862
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.6334861860197は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6398199132129565
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.70598666166558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8176049411834827
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.912216591233026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2531493320118305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 827.5889934323553は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9178147061075452
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 54.832925166428474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.739041414764612
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.764838423779055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.89013242305347
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.63667082905095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5137058512364512
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.974168370026418は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7762774581648253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 473.7542063910135は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.675553079027413
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.510748383327632は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5453997045299518
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 429.89124603770176は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.633358601580768
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 204.94296374748518は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3116330123910083
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0583561591573618は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.024631841543784283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 353.61701251063096は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5485331507464615
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 388.323128384407は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5891932577378918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3708882100441724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13700204141212025
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 138.40946482787925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.141165789412447
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4876651955871445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39579193008099234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.80635934427457は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4117267403743392
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 457.78098476132874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6606577490533803
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 62.865176979336574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7984101425259862
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.138958155006563は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0468445724632933
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.794070853196367は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5791054369545637
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.424920557233275は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4687152989886485
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.890298878245677は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9489163615316283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 148.3658935046465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.171334076380156
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9355673545926897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4676920494189636
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 314.8256179068305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.498070064420517
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.02759427327219は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.000119823874639
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.8236525965610095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6833760220115512
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.139436807693304は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9609194343720128
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 436.39592109885086は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.639880682675837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 246.70718690704226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3921818012473652
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 981.0503103208297は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9916912794843986
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.052866436595858は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.607762291675275
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 329.54495500745577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5179146674275823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0772784815729575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03232798498501077
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.82147412323343は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8439890137251902
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0937273254141893は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3209201210969469
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.202712549217374は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6919890461145868
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.429270905772205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8709461950342352
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 205.58280543249415は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.312986788250952
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 405.21307120578047は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6076834462168264
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2306576063990589は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09013724031131576
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 229.5724676349821は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3609198024054816
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.38202862005964は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5952980834579191
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3383435063564808は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12656759606890466
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9678906025982703は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2940009518145964
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.2873978812568は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2621519139943107
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 247.24014799193077は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3931189948779648
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.838604346125109は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8942387439684696
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.38246514905304は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37702655645216643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.183792346457569は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.621570121120785
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.87966314416393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.542572282013476
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1965573752842547は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3417425517597338
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 810.1379553541825は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908558979554674
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.977207708065244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4309969957533655
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.50476449409022は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0970755169477535
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.300677741586783は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7243314017920078
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.949556510744892は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28993582836677145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3920773664004509は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14366337239171878
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.028258877215336は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6437315113743818
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.650877119862045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.64982999457002
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.876443953655543は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8963301870482256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 575.0804409722537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7597285970842997
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7630153409796647は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44138329623910255
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.238690573559204は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9656104217638415
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.105586592293567は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8515999363494143
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.42163542891308は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0941787786903423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.81136063497798は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.651388130864428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.798462004171763は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6811020602643334
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.60376260693612は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5866296362726005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 617.7688734828157は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.790826022425767
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 925.5874579040525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9664174611122696
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.98546283826138は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.601902127411918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6244343042634592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2107021522012903
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.288534409871924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7233353344374116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.741977044599842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43806381462368005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4734635698723046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39330551829027705
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 118.62714692429701は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.074184085405321
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 911.765394541696は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9598831048161642
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 556.193283833002は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7452257403500084
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.095550427918704は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0041300024565771
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 266.31250482744076は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.425391559416975
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 407.5592670181493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6101907725050775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.745202803038993は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1971482588546536
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 399.0797272190994は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6010596666953245
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 319.8611274847325は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.504961463764403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.644815153485286は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.216117098436732
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 618.9972488795864は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7916887188116046
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 237.57961362223054は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.375809171699636
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6076881397479807は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5572289886702618
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.839302951057498は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.035001354689188
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 166.52791566084608は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2214870462582246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.627752719368456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1344242445327568
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 211.01886808995764は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3243212891412846
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.590868425776672は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7474792717915776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 357.67861009861844は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.55349296924067
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.124106918329661は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.494725888600271
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.807119111251941は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2569867788224782
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 785.753679483199は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8952864233841873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.2967481228278945は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6331398959058928
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 532.4934455692523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7263142664382407
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.90894049050151は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5429366678886156
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.07245850224141は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.705218502758851
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.64999861023942は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.246744675527503
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 731.8113482028721は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.864399139809886
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 180.58176179673438は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.256673885783631
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 616.1365385610507は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.789676964393003
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4604628931647712は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16449052707574152
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 710.8798544265168は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.851796206962282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.074113730089412は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03105026808166278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 90.98917768564147は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9589897401132794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 157.10519568124403は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1961905479832042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 93.94647067713608は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.972880469436701
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 194.1608817642663は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.288161735637875
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1637529273855372は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06586078644549886
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 197.17584043356442は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2948537006195617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.226006285021505は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5468634082481043
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0612692173526972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0258255674825566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.057128051455259は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.608218715163728
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.04678167848579は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0002031227397956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 437.1578236070244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.640638255157112
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 202.13588127978142は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3056434122716256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.762746101227062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2495101080876438
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 51.46828217701614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.711539673330941
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9119168914304465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2814690101275208
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.98101352055492は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4768463102649028
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.291052716106545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2378214348516257
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 847.915975175179は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.928352817674427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 260.7370585647421は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4162027618410438
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.644969298319855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5616938745946172
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 981.6050752332188は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9919367951754303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.07835868260117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6819496331366048
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.515755174888811は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6547303882845852
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 241.40051308065205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3827381888261985
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 217.31217179191327は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.337084052109848
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9551437855049927は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.597162276485102
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.191520436641426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5931921122771526
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 275.86425757548716は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.440695434646289
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.7341248116101は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7584671417677057
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 707.2741304675185は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8495877734498
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 55.415147899498706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7436284966767308
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 87.02203919926502は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9396292559575241
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4480085454570129は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16077112486794787
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 203.15091392343584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.30781878044541
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 85.47360674625472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.931832030353745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 350.38814980710583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5445494098236408
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.404103528440594は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.369292010551782
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.22425117895496は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6257497339554113
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 205.22906989756086は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3122388769169926
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.02528902491392は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1147873688646601
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 179.78570656319724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2547551612154355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.762400407910565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3377067966518046
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 83.87487881944641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9236319057185238
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.35198988722136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.675338234213239
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 837.3647425858506は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9229146708819775
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 466.42045527336137は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6687775885295695
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.240920922626827は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.121918191879074
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 249.8947929802858は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.397757206892801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 334.2907973258345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5241244210866745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8526044352832014は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45524155312073544
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.542298007029693は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.022935288579688
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.186469824257266は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3260585988265667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.98980731221539は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9493402664026787
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.33404513587196は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8471655957962834
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.185460642469645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1200953067489556
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.754034982512062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.070186978933199
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8541582548515314は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45547804982393336
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.30921131652751は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.871042651929941
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 97.18581022524114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9876028596717343
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.59365890559198は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4408092915321256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 654.6724348503557は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8160240552271607
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.26821865892218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.683661271454373
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5935678632321586は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20237056294604594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.491195814076152は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5429742081919559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 314.2140563825766は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.497225609325347
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 121.0907436791709は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.083110946423808
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.711356753106035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9872799085099898
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 904.0037611290817は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.956170237371611
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.02776788984838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9446196896398504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1622095801482242は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06528445102734703
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.658074548708804は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6498999943534776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.9503401557544455は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6946350419015632
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2455444665525846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09535923667677759
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.663300893430094は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1025469262931509
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.8379704235036は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0349479615013668
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 869.989833179365は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9395141774233315
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.61303329677202は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.608665427186518
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.56820476054737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3534970135041169
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 628.4105623965553は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7982434761005717
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.770650313079402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.106213013174991
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.631728319760022は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1652956286134901
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.917627098300354は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3205124164971336
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 475.6812198090596は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6773160055416234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.677979962012549は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5656093588305295
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.54267373182413は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5124532320450312
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.956946665701953は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3609141252582984
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.083814323946045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1487202908502054
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 138.1379544329678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1403130206215395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 549.7652820870708は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.740177310490929
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.935572479029766は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5432678643055917
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 827.9354097600947は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9179964572209496
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.971107074247867は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7760548590461349
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 439.90448516925625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.643358389970335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.957689135841692は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9981585641270382
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.633858351377328は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42059241494263644
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5760433082611593は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19756814734161965
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 600.5680282066999は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7785622084107557
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.912955666070916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2017508528236496
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 188.267621180912は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.274775635196706
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.53726199464575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0023270535913955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.149745439322515は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8542905793863094
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4778391560110786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5413094927695931
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.55916459546859は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.219038422984498
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.15692889692504は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8984889362545214
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 61.60158707929018は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7895919013023975
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.362343294067167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6397198393381764
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1852989961303504は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07382791658263743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 335.7104568039019は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5259648689855903
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.89802034093757は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1731285629004118
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.25261841124043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1854079034308342
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.892743012508393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6895524053817368
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 271.2157452641186は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.433314898627285
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 287.2698149914845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4582899946959604
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3346657050042747は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5230523030954807
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.771241216125497は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7612692265600848
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 401.77049454935246は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6039780396175223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.838693080937924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0349769185533675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1543411491238915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06233417735236835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 238.43945712639763は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3773781243666403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.644484063568353は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.35496243007979
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.932828920186942は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5947050548168729
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6404657076295026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2149671563051575
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.269663808741482は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9174878542954451
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 528.3187469183052は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7228960215116995
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.733435411755512は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43670881642052484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.18508962523253は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6353338252583791
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 155.66063087587068は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1921787862653552
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.387486821968132は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.14222886698483916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 137.9102485214948は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.139596541092092
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.45382672841914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7279788015475388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 248.04361780879108は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3945280570683023
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.97128791047856は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6124796159820116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 836.4136119199262は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.922421091976348
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.456773743635473は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.370268278807259
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1085507795295706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0447555916899115
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.45545951744704は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8600711151207892
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0912605512736462は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.037928455877675016
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.6354197033615705は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7509262660904216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.43274085187839は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1593488136862726
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 162.17964991514592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.209996358604971
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.629620961664466は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1344837783184238
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.07689004300187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9594081925598954
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.287655721559481は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.154960976816843
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 858.2266247939493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9336019835382197
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.47308955470774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8226458645027235
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.799135146073205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9444399880881117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 162.81975379696522は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2117070937017345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.238221582416685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5937093153632196
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.139700249515239は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4968881875014023
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 231.8057473975564は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.365124199669424
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.433293740907306は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4221512821016604
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 460.74771039278625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.66346318574407
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 314.7172334048646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.497920524825255
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.694878593701556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4098465700184657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.069223223440401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8493716955073564
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.198609131798533は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7158871653303936
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.77313536225364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.089103346932874
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.366237691368823は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4964624291896769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 680.5024098568923は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.83282966750511
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.50505757323039は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6946495699223147
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 149.48829094935957は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.174607176772616
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.900065845012765は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4456052282231302
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1384494373348777は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05631374678771228
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 93.49383278251138は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9707829640611751
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.721764899942は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8307282677522863
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 52.84700670510833は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7230203935683428
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 828.1816098766201は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9181255825805357
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.028348796470041は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0425104931960472
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.72977680196581は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.137663477188502
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.271676528292607は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9175935425868623
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1940387008709は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5043401740043586
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6298332145581387は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.212143164095293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 131.43759169569995は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1187195930103115
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 912.9856227634657は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9604639385379627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5678788481197532は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19531250118907906
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.29697160183091は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6655525836825607
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 456.36421158483677は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6593115793906974
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 317.965877347641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.502380515975729
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 810.6758679897114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.908847245232778
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.733148793541492は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4270501156259758
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0931794569259095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03869146181723193
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.78459956235184は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.157712372255054
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.16362424887456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4007731915400423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 151.1114393469681は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.179297342282216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.068891864449334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6634077659113977
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 92.4280069075911は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9658035881294549
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.87507804028311は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9771521461362154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.21617554624391は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5073397455130951
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 60.05151912227505は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7785239982181342
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 471.5282662420735は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.673507732078659
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.4371550953527255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6471046092165891
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.233556105218652は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1533134175777313
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.726651333510401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7579007419500539
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.036920970502077は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3018309852462053
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 513.1224115011854は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.710220983625831
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4202191940902886は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5340539398963117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 136.5963446283538は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.135439077610695
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.29842682507685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3074623803928622
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3892882898235555は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3782685545744162
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6675173187880885は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42610724775149666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5843836395151076は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19986034919236972
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.987169395929736は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7772215458819133
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.846235927330913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.585035920254875
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 510.78368554158226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.708237017423764
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9908596997948345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4757960409035912
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 83.6905200717915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9226762666709267
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4375047274772232は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1576092816148127
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1362057353830084は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05545697719516118
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.816129339425476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1991002078464037
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.630953280696803は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9360587657826809
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 142.61167418289926は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.154155078290685
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 985.6250896256688は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.993711750164602
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 796.3234498439285は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9010895048608383
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.5867709582445215は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5547036446585542
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.023724556342065は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0800390187239868
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.979006236983224は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3005738824621385
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.729200718513587は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6747877468961557
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.183459534643433は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9129369392680378
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 202.56015031182983は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3065540106100397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.239918624692046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7193245424948668
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.550182622390967は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0625888510047568
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1249456832255493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.051131553518576345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.79770805913718は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4885183978541376
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 50.61211691356474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7042545025854683
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.970745741181982は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3418447981942339
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 688.3090951672674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.837783508264846
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.421119930341515は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5341682990235829
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6020455998479735は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5565492064393718
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 186.69135867797814は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.271124216367272
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 493.5445668593745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6933263753788985
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 557.0459071722006は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.745890987651309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 847.500787537763は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9281401104422535
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.932101025713646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9970411283902619
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 992.7054595023861は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.996820410340521
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.880836642013217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8376412473807063
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.45121129337281は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8659989621914912
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.883502979443513は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2524525913970366
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.02008317285856は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48001890355851495
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 96.18244077630554は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9830957937632738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.279934763395163は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6314371493605035
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4168656529902774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15132867245558812
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.302380902421664は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2856108814953155
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.43799872592945は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8158300089460315
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 400.80704193374305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.602935343213731
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 678.3602957182262は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.831460420830177
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.781332249419386は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6792582546751633
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9834828305177266は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6002629496232182
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 116.90015074274393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.067815071184934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.428099340287505は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8080825797598392
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 130.00681897126347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.113966132029341
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 175.61530830098903は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2445623704588846
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 742.7520398958516は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.870843853224669
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.71227196095768は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.353555172281294
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 335.82068663481425は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5261074452702617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.5261886680988885は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8146596248195952
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 578.6959038794995は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7624504083548613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 82.96224555637133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9188804986792287
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 207.79178023773386は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3176283638756328
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.9290630266194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4302212427747463
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 995.0016690976511は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9978238092676266
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.51515253343974は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2903719501431345
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.172037141882597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7136616350128305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.999406467627075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47703532360743517
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.128918823001422は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1798078925980686
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.32225436079315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1502105566473517
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.958616564496938は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6953605268510239
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.53944090798345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4399551191800786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.697955178597134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.501031246971848
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.973227110474239は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29517707367054224
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 750.0896233469587は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.875113157524523
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 545.6112117269133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.736883286027276
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.846026337809252は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6853857701675914
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 562.2977686747979は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.749966360133722
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.80546041664182は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6415282493399261
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 116.61255195076964は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0667452995616333
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 350.9015647717169は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5451853048646136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4370196511939906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1574627071368414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 478.48637163709697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6798695726100523
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.555293546291397は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6585163684499216
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 507.308667949252は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7052722827991103
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.4280699735754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0018551165023384
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.11077334026534は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.644544671799395
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 478.7948971882371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.680149513215576
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.51528687084264は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.088190281267439
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.1267317387021は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.352427066556828
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 129.8228190429142は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.113351035402787
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.809357034746111は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8926152787228012
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.27985967041964は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8590173007175943
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.14932376793897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6546512499750632
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 244.54270395923348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.388354709980802
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.42700021623078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3309613739942785
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 541.8582686039367は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.733885704965304
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.930944054006048は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4761204151689418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.44568444093774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.265894774683861
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.93649886679967は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5176774320030781
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.772512886924243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4111567654550266
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.958425149345372は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.998190663420989
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.05934310733808は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.959324513028098
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.244853890433205は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4947784981272236
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.485781296412505は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6673201346360251
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5330519308456354は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18555686646410052
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.317339753176163は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7256944105898123
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.0650781718782は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1494195138650847
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 950.5155413797357は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.97795922218019
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.5100628089383767は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5453148877852821
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.610225812008611は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1007228635779365
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 806.0749340037913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.906375416385317
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9135473321214096は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2818392090872559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.17266524914142は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4341322385734274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.937468439567844は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6935043326212836
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.322382412118802は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.328835728057696
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 511.1334252052776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.708534282261349
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 275.12398836714607は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.439528458660454
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.665012674941425は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6688528280717237
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.519173554543938は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5464406853978835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.675569746248584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5400236055959076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.8134140496333355は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.581313962291372
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.59103151361776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6393971460392893
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.62869003933334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5597498725939682
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.541870439938826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8030599947182007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 462.92207456674214は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6655078907286884
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.341581701459432は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0913708225980125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.073387651298515は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3166805076320287
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.996440367351815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7778935191209122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.4914056241064575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6523822784776112
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.005414306131243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8454338249245601
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.846701763537615は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7669109413226117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 438.15279694405586は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6416255883526194
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 254.72121034952585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4060651096837975
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3340544382814978は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12517355204145364
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 80.38175329238877は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9051574748207485
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.035373987296214は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30864421980017986
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.566547961227606は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5522480685800142
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.704956649141495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1674637485257549
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.707787282519178は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.410064697710654
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0421309284696847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.017922285124591042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.735577480680805は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43704901995632894
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.099353679589893は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4785571701320068
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.043959488786808は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1773621552595324
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 307.9034497595498は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.488414554778948
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 148.37141854741998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1713502489037424
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 273.7806283073531は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.437402715832845
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 753.8329885174327は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8772751387087125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.1257927799277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4001197736928699
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.10636692558952は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5328354600053968
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.360197199055645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8034705812355223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 402.506942803986は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6047733758727203
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 81.63432118142772は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9118727857874191
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0009434347399702は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.0004095353470299212
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 525.2906410330687は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.720399663160042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.096960346815551は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04019092887785647
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.835253704496933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9927855672082725
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.067532209710513は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6093310006855168
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 55.5117587507316は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7443849870803358
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.728002833681352は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.674677728163344
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.80944405217033は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.824837857832443
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.99761609157952は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1875139979385034
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.610709641072885は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0257444303571297
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.029087339522379は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1769326083018865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.08707266930814は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1488207549511436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.67398988363745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.849259610000647
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.226338707164429は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6259642993319942
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.479927700932354は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7387748286863298
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 327.4884815347647は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5151960295373796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0893095857843849は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03715132538500665
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6874241274675685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22722425453242612
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.743307197982592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3168779990795714
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.951467700694345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4700380348934936
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 434.7010503106049は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.638190689520372
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6782801912640914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22486446862708065
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0826248129498315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3186110383866586
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.7021782517167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1513765262914246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.710468254584112は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5694287202753165
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.887262775870305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6521231229427569
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 227.67298061615801は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.357311493216921
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 62.2523409723352は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.79415568753085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 529.5350258607688は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7238946916105755
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.132957444721036は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.41718856124829
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.79857392726947は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8561158183137727
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 267.11713313724573は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4267017449600763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.025489109535198は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.010931052618687542
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.054606708275605は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.956869591244763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.272835145793757は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.797463874144561
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 161.02926760141654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.206904817662984
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.48190949080903は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.439046904970882
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1826089440855265は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07284115924984569
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 811.9706919914929は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.90954035370413
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 174.17072672649573は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.240975163935362
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.02181738489406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1492863072432016
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 134.59855767692582は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1290404061263803
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 102.26245073605789は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.009716196452252
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.576479497413128は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8794674523324483
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.423223756874062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4686902544934757
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 497.8466545578725は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6970955930914076
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 445.6062656599631は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6489512888138242
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.25518211684319は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3274648304041166
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 626.3589589049876は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7968232935820976
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.81442782922922は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1706848825857585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.899314123293944は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1731662765112842
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.880668478691334は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.412975489649582
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.331933584302874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6366817895525705
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 181.84621093542847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.259704256245947
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 506.84984271066094は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.704879316057168
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3552517430742648は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37203733387886573
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 747.9061215347541は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.873847087893692
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.319935460997723は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2629239393655691
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.117643017609852は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0834181541544203
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 318.8122094311623は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5035349450548336
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 723.0107673071697は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8591447649947646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 180.0822524949883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2554709142449396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 84.28978309933493は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9257749362797032
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.057504615060586は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6082590224709636
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.500072020804043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5440769808976957
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.55506165881723は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4556831022719399
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.77846627198902は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25004563335202157
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 52.537263502902654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7204674480362765
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 523.9968932807981は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.719328712107761
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 217.11442581056914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.336688680394941
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 41.845107211386484は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6216446849022776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.81361271381624は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9918289149072419
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 60.18224836732631は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7794684086497092
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.486429702845722は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39557618522609017
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.326291529580686は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3488165913207733
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.708531895514565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2946542745369989
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 415.71776396367625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.618798582664909
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.25997859645213は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5132147486957771
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.79469972907569は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8047845976234171
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 532.3186305302814は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7261716662383275
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 287.89456327285467は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4592334635481303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.347537876109364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6058170379566197
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.16052622264783は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8460928376945742
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.408149324348594は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3816834131214749
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.436066689242819は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.646998066456485
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.3612111620708は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.239580019380567
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.662630424082353は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2207957232909754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 394.26850093509745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.595792081621748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 192.46994113320918は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.28436291348448
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.567788336681557は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1922269181943095
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8754978708178287は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4587130503575274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.745466748424164は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8890475938392277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.300218843614566は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2121934351975892
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.428501451188577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3102365097871478
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3643534969507318は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13492690835931986
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.421279899608636は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.80762160095623
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 675.9546251334128は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.829917543995532
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.275042713627052は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6309404582922286
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 278.98875376107725は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4455866969010263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 214.37278645712985は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3311696530280486
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.189477511234267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1202275917190532
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 107.1070521361171は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.029818066564553
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.62774562071826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.976018493730093
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.99834016311516は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5314577148188373
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.79339880247241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8247335432342027
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.332898701724926は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.36789588142683993
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.646354130408845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.564030774071111
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 81.8590877576014は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9130669005334457
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.573446109062847は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7461238061910199
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 184.5755601197461は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2661741950224226
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.36978950918474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5233534672095463
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 516.6641084211195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7132082930609354
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0275486491277595は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4810911304700801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.653701971497は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5270328444102932
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.872602037479254は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.578325144352355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.479786697488063は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17019911892194173
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.81968382384347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8337642402366656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1097298318756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3242268439052822
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.733125457519107は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6751480161489894
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 168.05125379069776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2254417569860987
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.67359689211786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9622442716004724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.187591513036786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5463895416747881
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.030901669874385は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4917943951317532
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.715494802673044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0300122299843837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.470782879000782は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5404274464570119
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.662179143635876は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42523727671144773
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 503.1649712998133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.701710399327676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.874512904254093は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1097308068785625
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3881466754341787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5299622030024878
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.72602038813478は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6787552224339393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2326875073312211は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09085299464738339
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.24074960762289は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.183006328056605
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.611660314699766は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8203105328544849
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.39839463916233は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9513297200754125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6769823671080983は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5654915472237674
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 132.8624567969371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.123402278840801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 833.4283787508544は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.920868284368277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 339.9493152774914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5314141707594118
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 641.6144344213315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8072741257234552
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 185.01281256303676は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2672018053367804
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 367.0366616227778は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5647094461192785
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 114.71159613492259は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.059607322721228
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.459828192022098は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2164252977264232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.23921446084077は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5345237922423922
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.085905363548218は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2807127660701387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8178963626435527は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.44992501646684613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.688303987649075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3745339676382278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1896749258559396は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3403796452575013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3283531567872706は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5222294011243206
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 241.1773527989738は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.382336523964738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 678.7600742090558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8317162884767324
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0782344376113557は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.48830169252072375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 490.5230708944838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6906594384775104
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.768953632749124は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6605709837247071
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 262.2553876537718は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4187244189028467
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.031134066078401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3077385901878986
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 194.81999769787046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2896335338777174
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.882399027981997は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9485302792810403
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 64.56801367309818は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8100174262682898
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2652942100720792は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10219152073278104
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.08040481766684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6819681155949069
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.033264694948457は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30819391974605237
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.863346833205584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9475977440916594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.335279670527001は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0544322397574861
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.55233108236315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8546237870785491
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 95.5327242810526は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.980152162581497
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.637929633345318は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.822032644274481
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 401.9864020687518は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.604211362521317
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.320131874850198は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4520952713477595
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6106466561874577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.41674809524216827
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.874809651153893は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.33994428259432
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.48735677511406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5424963802802423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.783375757077081は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5778794766670595
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0998459617324103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49134011330790384
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.883771755767672は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4599608839484681
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.493638771437042は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5432779986200988
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.485436186324364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6944774026798142
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.106762958362552は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9088474744382488
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.257858853809432は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6291912606655465
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 178.32380378625928は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.251209319412086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 884.1864016284183は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9465438313760597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.877092737907136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.588506189214495
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.614577095103954は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3543884706147682
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.880486594781754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3400569759373901
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.96873817449628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1874325505992007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2522306793238855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09768433968057433
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 516.4952643390832は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.713066343898557
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0904259118162998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.037596163099110846
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 227.42731874541002は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.356842631274215
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 735.1959131341058は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8664030841938337
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.001901257495136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7782888461908423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.90893347595754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2530697232416534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.567639010092462は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.40953396529047503
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 90.8679509545616は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9584107349507205
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 180.8447097794159は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2573058089383253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.362150649589275は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7586254257444653
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.90399878099796は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1431397210287941
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 115.55104206595966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0627738664006356
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.194734657415772は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3653894086513172
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9570319832845307は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29159792328216183
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.85398993066477は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2267027301181497
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 834.0117434771915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9211721658552876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9945600523492102は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29984711661039487
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 160.51894888405593は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2055263072083937
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 318.2746002859105は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5028019813925435
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.065634768536639は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.027608381812405103
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.55210479350174は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1509163314433137
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 120.03111091623252は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0792938256150886
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.781548942378855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5536591367502912
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5975191397105095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20344607009858495
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.61940547864451は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0154410961726352
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.726320005145376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43557683033659744
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.40861946225736は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9735259035644938
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.722175839530787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7575611993211423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.35851504329187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.168375236415792
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.783794241530883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.032771592783581
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.2028739318562は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.28336623075267
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.534801255436268は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8152323838094685
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 407.03983126514197は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6096369095992995
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4200037826952139は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15228950128550012
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0738308800298082は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.030935888762733232
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 405.6326879514089は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.60813294540049
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4249281373414933は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3846988728275662
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 72.45889087722722は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8600916820365456
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.86419414746641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4751508002808005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 119.29739968086116は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0766309774795557
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.418231962214335は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4686165680472714
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 273.0445683981036は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.436233541654591
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.05902528879739は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8264572366148237
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.662160640084597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7529821864901681
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.114480662585038は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3446767448350867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 438.5256947963659は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6419950453219974
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 507.63780700225686は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.705553959287551
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 960.8471615557359は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9826543115271806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 266.3944685367301は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.425525202822154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.29470424908111は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0126138745250013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.289311983224204は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6323876358089193
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.902168803667102は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3598766113733054
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 555.1774456483016は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7444318143822257
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 154.21425276618513は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1881245138683516
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 271.10331365213716は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.433134825924429
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.586030960393215は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8800146108292675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.424813007846668は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7343847727399265
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 128.91518017521958は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.110304059930309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.140181775291424は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0842251894917094
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.245046975951597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0105139540841916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.84132951053243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3773304701532765
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.10159671361789は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.303230555747445
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 223.318206251229は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.348924130828393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2894997582685574は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.359740602009758
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.057309825190378は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0812504207061528
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.080957505354455は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6442510194820106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.467535787917337は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1894211295394306
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.348250688945603は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0916054377618392
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7433142947052043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.24137569127019964
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.25376323843384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5123859481144707
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.285142087880578は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6319652269498597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 560.911632021441は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7488944463749014
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 629.1311132597364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7987411634601465
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.59918063245905は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.629401245811078
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.301933065814282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9685732101215206
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 919.9537336473508は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.963765986338045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 85.92912870703593は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9341404082122975
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2430628877590684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09449310057717619
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.645254917465546は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.422467530402982
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.744742413203483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2238784711123873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 209.86175707169787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.32193330468085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 479.2111581608371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.680526921800416
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.210900607356317は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08310849702562995
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.528032956240956は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3330043495969577
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.80046000859476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.599888091622427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.943669474304045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1120574143950024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.73639793044542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8735321623304628
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5699234875375216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4099201935900896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5137655740988931は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18005862433305153
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 196.78423037760055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2939902925994047
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.137828068741545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.493288316303489
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.993360305618552は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9539219931251632
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.092863889207315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.569290365905136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.5826020499192675は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8183976006870721
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.278642695260277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3852244037197083
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.977666350857037は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9531634610930075
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 978.492130357694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.990557337141724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 157.3379586246804は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1968335111325397
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 114.18118829193394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0575945584284536
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 320.54202400972963は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.505884974881713
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 156.88943571211482は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.195593700971263
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 99.11738420275817は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9961498320958304
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.68639197134702は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2941661279960628
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 998.1100784996925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9991784409353475
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3407216983056043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3693497810289387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.01112475909844は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8261469074833023
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.424012356261943は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6458163312823753
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 209.03212438354535は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3202130342948513
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.721020504551294は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7574735043112935
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.324499011496483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0540189982031718
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.50413678336043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2175928143357013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 298.11392755510434は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4743822662675607
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 546.5826601247819は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.737655849947981
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.75072101860655は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.540963819894583
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5595139564463232は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19298926571099106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.89763273734642は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5669985037718839
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.99657771133486は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4149161795512675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 135.08376873834337は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1306031686307865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 501.21459706413305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7000237106303553
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.5763297470463は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.407838222512907
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0668197603291472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.028091051377071574
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 993.4620993209359は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9971513033836796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 47.432123370762035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6760725669365764
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9631961998316267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5980455728123749
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 424.0716805884953は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6274392713401644
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.433666537075815は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.535758116060813
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.768760814182556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5995420586765225
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.53677790725096は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.55067804810244
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.410384092522234は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9248158299779236
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 396.43113452183394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5981677553491713
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.93488850770137は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9774258446915856
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5006282013291594は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17627310389380102
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.37739407573512は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13905821072344116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.353114980598594は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8664713570840854
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.423476807919702は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5344673901187418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 297.78638863922583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4739048429327037
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.87481790032109は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4896044048063803
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.8546049913888は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9535403393314825
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 71.5196886457577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8544256151317695
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.012362991964151は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30370632190478253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 643.282140532434は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8084014942328235
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.90604065683828は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5302770784457114
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.109279213274654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6345707615151177
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.9893379062068406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.47557500922013507
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 140.62817863752187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.148072351982614
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2974933557993398は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11310514259211668
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 539.6847853620009は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.732140174732869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 430.46377486290424は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6339366098219674
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1834251948617927は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3391383173861646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.884955075655564は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4601390547372275
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 243.3058254559822は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3861525073406007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.5611042821683503は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.408427262282654
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.215382177342139は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08471286345879281
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2106661807310872は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.34452316735851796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 404.9955106064606は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6074502090673906
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 562.8070850012078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.750359555993627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 818.9453631598078は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.913254928293114
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2935867147718925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11179554668584823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9179275347235882は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5930563991011073
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.95532916299358は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1447400846072244
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.782871233496621は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9904663371860601
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 216.97138176546846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3364024547657185
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.773089100566443は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5766970610789283
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 58.54212269312912は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7674684655729922
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.02668931809705は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4154189279123441
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.40516363713469は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0571015207564471
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.93271836609585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3410924619662377
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 111.3915695262849は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.046852323272534
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.981560515028015は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9991984441015288
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9971123646719258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3004025005162406
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 286.3175339727196は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4568479448585747
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 732.3663434237046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8647283776815082
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.554528786317967は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4073108009969896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.609565976772543は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8201729420754467
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 288.6415178611996は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.460358799665236
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.65557409104349は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6959680073349919
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.5300891717254は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8483744329267484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.41503056352035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8476653721258818
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4128898531128342は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.15010830618694004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 606.9341287742965は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.783141559177094
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.5982008975217035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8807107721789095
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.11824620079609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2334592682656453
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4168531293079023は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3832502593984721
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.422093341696431は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1278202547188916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 388.18277182006943は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5890362567877676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 242.99933412385215は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3856050835294527
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 152.84296387037773は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1842454507650606
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.3094518548074は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5093295900680375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7058679234725647は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5688899370742996
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4473198194310117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.16056450932692357
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.289992694957225は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7986501410666347
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.204680678993597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0493994841350585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.183868954256848は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.326005281174487
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.249562124419088は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1832573735399359
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 289.98933398616595は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.462382024532961
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 614.1946295432684は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7883060146959124
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 147.3670005546066は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1684002441639922
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 96.37962109538978は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.983985214593278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.13893988574368は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.820457229503274
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 154.059242864016は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1876877591568347
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 138.58384240377868は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.14171259850139
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.645652088294295は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.667046682478506
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 667.525588065676は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8244679180407055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 159.27472928082315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.202146875584595
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 776.8573445612371は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8903412759979354
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.004511110002756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4150486933646906
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 404.9263697475172は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6073760599566813
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 142.09230576859306は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1525705617225936
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.997424280804669は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2040500632382827
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.8249592279972は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6834936478081748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 121.39406430882288は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0841974519703217
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 68.76427879895617は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8373628924617913
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.061346798588776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3628846667971675
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.16862333304012は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0869596800223182
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.840619453519036は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9930224375347511
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 123.24646757604297は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0907744806128212
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8746124047367843は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2729114865251506
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 164.88318074639355は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.217176356787186
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 334.95526746479095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5249868118417176
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 541.3818239462377は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.733503670916644
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.16938196999954は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.645121322534446
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0936248643072095は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.038868375653275056
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8046957795354646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2564040026935597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.16597880578838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06669065624391246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 527.4771467076114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7222036482848404
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5203163865434355は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18193397651818988
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.52399335263483は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4846413503039073
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 727.3954775173885は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.861770596560117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0150616841981996は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.006492434656039325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 90.14504513642223は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9549418605198896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.099743773916243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3221663021798855
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7325230371668245は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.23867901808783465
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.80863429317043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2743572622982349
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 926.8264931778375は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9669984395293483
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7388917876147は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43757487381285387
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.715439767613852は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.104331384987172
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.36014996142718は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1335867935392796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4828863028577084は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.39495683265482373
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1797993611032611は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07180815664970508
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0195492914710194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.008408227167993942
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.813488024594086は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5417475381922081
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.25773723699727は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2110601000606582
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 117.89209418706545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0714846823974384
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 165.99152958600644は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2200859269080393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 863.3841036027964は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9362040482800102
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.2666431614627998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5141016960084257
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.561633793168795は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6591204172865818
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.280072568466652は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7979646621930141
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 551.9294752807929は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7418835877778625
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 276.93204563679495は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.442373213737521
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 836.110550415026は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9222637035885923
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 300.07624520497865は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.477231616935253
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 360.34629164891754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.556720057060928
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0681668697553124は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3155855768252943
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 807.9656154122559は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.907392878900245
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 294.98715999726005は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.469803112711392
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.695836992953575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8862558602498047
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.09483252216776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.149511108380829
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.548688790152816は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6584758794561616
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 737.8466674238322は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8679661200744437
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 741.3944902021276は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.870049354173038
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5199050079082217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1818164459510656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.3808814006390575は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7308534199194467
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.289985319059079は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1105847677504801
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7078505180737773は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4326246862437042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.973216509370292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4467424067346029
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.550169103588914は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7443062154896529
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.45192732913998は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9611928625690256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.07971769728738は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5062305378212977
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.26050526462691は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.35420552282607676
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 521.4661389041584は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7172261130223436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 124.41963342408819は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0948889174524776
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.905066944993195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3599315654331523
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.511008720311674は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7412310982292893
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.150501917742181は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9614449163754574
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.041322629473406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4156630381179132
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9088705358263098は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2807764745000726
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.43230623929017は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.185916812965307
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.559926333432818は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1920075365444567
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.853397859571956は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3589507804214045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 322.83158269436296は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5089760152660627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6752584843242264は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4273657500552952
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.467676654681604は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.388592732573868
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 813.4783718258798は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9103460107190484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.032722458355685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4818326673763186
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 145.07031556236987は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1615785557434792
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.5389095126847123は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5488694581887668
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 480.29891620501604は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.681511606654136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 393.40583888469394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5948408013804327
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 140.63908332225787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1481060270315844
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.442366384322551は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8090454199814727
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 524.7012611194177は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.719912108026328
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 411.4756922138873は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6143441845077353
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 550.1115341916658は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7404507509001004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.564436873971162は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.408992012965659
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.634005280457046は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5638844036797592
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7689046100371197は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2477044137737745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.324603829258927は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12208600620205012
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2832746616074062は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.10831961916081201
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.326977244482975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5095650975155213
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 284.2359707745243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4536790381246956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.61080866882679は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8488711852718378
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 122.7723160667531は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0891004487687024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 241.35772809320832は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3826612091605233
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 23.81494664311776は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.376849612821135
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.685327870916492は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1362552066291594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.98316527503393は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8449935813362721
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 663.2663777729941は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.821687982647763
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 399.399993745948は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6014080537342323
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.81378058489949は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8739816016177624
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.822245330536067は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1079640820687526
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6213688500844952は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20988182504836783
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.020223941531615は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3014689310867316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.893735223029257は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1103787475907678
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3571811339157343は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1326378139164638
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.59762025783031は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1334629084198182
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.3827511135010457は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5292700456716962
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 519.7292200112907は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.715777134242389
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.850307765063711は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.108913529151227
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.482956555052771は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0963174590222884
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 171.18582658841527は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2334678042123084
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 441.73274789007394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.645159596905566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.490252462621726は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7519735156617742
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.9640123463254975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7755385338311724
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.1693725688466365は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6200707047604305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 127.20143938499609は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.104492025726108
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.856434982036742は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1416515082856495
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 834.2056282342957は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.921273115625914
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.013300665963014は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1465404402239443
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.498590216993679は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7402513550465374
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 61.36437029775156は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7879162819808472
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 207.545910683151は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.317114180811439
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.646256436126535は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7607711093423917
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 350.17291750937216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5442825545656627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.550037802181365は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2911476014895786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 266.62492371308343は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4259007441968508
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.140461312914119は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05708055758908981
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.329608694690613は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4204444047574385
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.998358987460357は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6018817840977497
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.258372224411268は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7208513252633396
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.803572787732644は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4441006067921494
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.089342679844915は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2065383016287077
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 36.40909262264645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5612098557016436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.7799940028646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.29622615558658
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 152.89508601982206は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1843935276048
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 166.9047271621993は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.222468637166875
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.426745361126756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6377572821674655
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 21.739810875468216は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3372557616409007
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 855.0732520836016は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.932003321293069
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.40174673963054は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.97320854816447
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 157.62986613590326は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1976385067395876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 169.9922458214611は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.230429111532649
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.662835235115011は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2208492185367812
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.47351084647399は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8777945527976292
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7812829289949472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5776391740311969
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9047477865068405は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.27983747755497224
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 969.7117137202856は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.986642641741284
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 119.86313009908676は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.078685614650401
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.795227296502719は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8322039882158142
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 139.39401544682406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1442441287532934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 556.389745697114は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7453791173153412
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.347869027018355は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.286633138824143
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.63395045834419は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5395020313822418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.058632286152685は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0812980520610787
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.89123312920388は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6323685324482176
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.339647199353223は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4523944394072843
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 349.75476246529274は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.543763636811657
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 51.803695091111855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7143607385183217
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.515437129121157は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.217890073047282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.543419812468542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4239568759513384
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.456326937123173は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0590453989025472
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.095329692687766は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.03954486087824716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 56.48846646275217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.751959784759256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.7484514162607896は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43908806444661563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 411.06692514704406は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6139125344208436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.781385423556187は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7620319231450474
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.884774593472101は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46011188451578544
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.98496377402395は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4911509927319233
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 149.38231858238836は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.174299195896138
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.25196608302193は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9457243894082585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.044239717583882は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6068368899798916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.259839443247913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8609270160606294
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.152996427932347は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7890866629622818
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.621632418066309は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6647954008675119
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.840497967502756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6516704269233318
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 259.46307551662966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.414075561643519
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.499520301322118は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8128813046156967
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.098597077721255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04083843945939669
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.197915954194777は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3053065607196057
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.13895944410004は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0059933858775745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6697185197364157は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42646547418500735
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1304342872128301は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05324532163022622
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.874450232424999は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7689672288678293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 149.99800985221285は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.176085496949442
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.69799684172529は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1037352147196335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 727.201212951179は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8616545946055014
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.765615464913857は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1060417581588613
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.550214951271017は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4065767875777042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 768.7844164755768は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.885804571451256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 214.6238084798404は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.331677897116827
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 526.2800101414318は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.721216874387135
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.18760008001842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5819223657638548
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.855903393802215は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4602346753454867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 512.7236677238271は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7098833652746412
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2148847740828344は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08453508916639552
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 259.05663239351946は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4133947156157465
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.381243055949476は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6935620180694806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.257035511209477は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.306575889428769
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.1165032557881425は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6145284632360041
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.22467462017774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5343393279139002
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 79.90950465467878は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.902598438557829
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.24327501056058は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8878606789973364
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.181584186051445は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.570327889701707
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 266.5082183019999は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4257106058885856
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.344402049449577は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12852916585037333
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 356.87220689787154は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5525127265465923
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8772369513637217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2735190942382094
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.556064681675194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6585898810557053
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.48498144234801は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6072939445387706
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.89376169811258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1730044008016516
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1132016300359364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.04657383359004541
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 241.5189761679237は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3829512589850497
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 419.67954383453645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.622917801195546
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.024629203602283は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7799303226518981
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.851573358666146は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7672726539653028
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.493144575178619は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8124550729025225
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 217.34260718185152は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3371448724323924
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 86.65819546338035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9378096412128265
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.3848504684473735は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8051507306536835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.421847142550604は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6850413524026169
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 146.28618941524238は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1652033271925277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.868350612799093は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.200531787688281
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 384.44388250034785は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.584832954542877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.945095693792は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5177907733564786
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.809950015634392は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.250662700599424
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.399583477549484は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.287792405427969
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 343.5398882505169は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5359771700458063
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 27.9545686737869は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4464527956811022
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.428652810403541は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.188328006260765
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.959823627654073は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8425982340779276
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.370854567980561は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7300433927071597
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.470074255959053は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0199497617971716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.604104520680832は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.20523266274866914
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 572.1838818029477は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.75753561973518
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 780.3033795586192は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.89226348788501
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 518.5414320170082は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7147834627067065
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.347228166466643は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2866187534253979
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.363004756926962は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2869727521509071
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.775701996051287は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0324455723901258
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 78.17529492535105は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.893069528344276
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.803061658076523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5801333665752235
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.0955773919085345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6123151369738685
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 739.6131258900043は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.869004609965523
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.0618900550942105は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4859895922005335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 204.64711696672202は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.311005630758648
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.989079575808745は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5183701985182538
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 404.7687182844328は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6072069415753085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.033661024621961は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.014378141009212309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 118.13042689223533は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.072361773392145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.961261597954467は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1749682166520055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.33931067557929は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.758452467620029
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 84.9974171887413は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9294057290352362
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.98834003931102は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6019333764583499
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.165516938570805は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9621569643596236
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 41.0362308242995は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.613167464009661
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.466335795864207は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4693261337265389
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 988.8541233507372は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9951322288099593
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 55.95990604319842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.747876976639041
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.681445256585512は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.392370586827278
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.219182256073383は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5077455652430157
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.664812510484548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.93775916987245
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 865.7394157100136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9373871906900693
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 112.8574205170741は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.052530119759974
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 270.1873598720472は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4316650276385414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 121.77767798788554は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.085567688829504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 500.7525593832641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.699623177682415
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.4666458266444615は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3921067957904165
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 133.7897006588206は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.126422682047617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.036003128946134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7807494562333879
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.083628288626559は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3188202450512223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.932161075008523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1741226660660853
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 24.69243206065314は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3925638675140841
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 883.9598581476098は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.94643254354156
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 308.24405736235724は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4888947125845116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.050861096555737は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7033654251686848
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.66138725664992は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7608850867282309
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.699179419571426は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4264979138354188
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 675.1319794876774は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.829388680031619
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.6262104262556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2928364509068593
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 162.4385125885269は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2106890041031964
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8198291366350097は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2600306140839692
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2421118534184301は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09416070625531359
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.568701914550324は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.932915034986507
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.310428293816641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8639428215806192
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 49.586990560041485は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6953677517106043
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4586573239428953は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5389075352167525
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 153.77312573848403は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1868804423360415
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 841.0411875569913は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9248172646334916
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 66.61810191388416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8235922545924805
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 463.0032448583602は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.665584034687807
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 163.40434376496057は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2132635971662795
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.965127410717782は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4720433596169129
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 148.0326749211916は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1703575868255793
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 76.44614185131852は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8833555719594033
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.256801264420258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2110350966163987
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 283.3194139777727は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4522763348259042
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.41785594722537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5845331237669134
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.79804712145394は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6702277303802733
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 114.49553627821597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0587885556057968
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 160.91727581093195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2066026717348297
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.103525362187677は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9086739957012552
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.077380581255362は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2571355012764096
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.442040202894427は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.38775280938424683
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5523181646118895は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.19098073945686955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.137433434470238は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8535420709313732
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 164.64429310256526は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2165466818015336
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6764388024488044は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.565427341155034
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 200.17554821443906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.30141102656939
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.963787483950181は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8428455091489081
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 211.46840511809725は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3252454898772115
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 786.1118753762032は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.895484356982241
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 113.3391576361385は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0543799805364964
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.36737441124058は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.865502977312293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.583437580238288は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9815213185087002
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.226833595642248は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.087314001599865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.92725773640966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2285866068739306
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.37933881998382は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3091900898033533
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.010938013939496は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1464672117055448
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 369.78894267058587は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5679539208606217
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.678811070600167は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6701355088270605
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.138215956978585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3300515662552148
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 378.5568012036902は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5781310531849044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.683111028764877は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4725094165470145
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 550.8183837419111は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7410084265457315
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.096982206361947は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4785229515131406
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.12367042452756は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4946652056278976
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.333498782329115は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6368386788673824
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.406214305084883は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8066014628883782
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.6931731990493555は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6714665819140552
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.36662659795738は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8411505746276056
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 521.1352668227787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.716950464201627
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 855.2485161735461は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9320923293719203
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3384683443383227は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12660810429264935
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1877158881444103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3399909208502412
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 336.5493061805342は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5270486995658414
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.43335210078469は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8711847048204634
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.31056870746121は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3527815637774436
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 175.20554002809823は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.243547834512388
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 551.913882885838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7418713184807038
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2353483857251877は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.09178945205832811
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 75.08814162682677は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8755713560098448
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.680974569351769は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42829269445935136
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.240765163455999は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7952378406270189
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.894731839770072は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1428501695637738
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7324211847435567は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2386534858180066
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.3011935513487645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7243736609983927
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.388081474759501は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6422746826469695
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 220.4355168405133は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3432815698764538
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1130466155997065は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.046513353439630256
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.350746748717459は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.728414396267225
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.84313958240802は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1412345979736558
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.197776281309109は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.120500762257924
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5287183056242002は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.18432746606383132
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.61445809997306は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5265261143684181
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3238075869576376は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3662001652922918
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.722491728533996は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.069019934969999
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.966661794118728は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0400744502709363
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.811409902083787は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1989705976611316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.67199753266408は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1573721299844646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 387.65787864934305は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5884486148737293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.88772306270543は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5300423892999622
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 189.25507136803262は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2770475258875282
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 918.5794222031545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9631167122296085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 502.61297205121565は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.701233693205146
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.8002593235771363は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5798132331841499
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.273376867211137は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9176828076734874
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 96.8299019443243は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.98600949206125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.112495204770778は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7862185314294423
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.891241671722189は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8971453439888865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 78.71247791235842は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8960435844420271
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.46672810568936は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5374000581950722
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.351166531978802は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9217471441083009
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.107784112049626は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.49245084211019896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 234.65741027555134は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.370434273404538
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 30.557170864643634は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4851131426146917
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 42.6085168727585は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6294964174394335
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 409.32955963259315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6120731082460016
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.63565661070258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4208888270936312
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1693964862749837は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06796178456396551
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 62.62266371776032は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.796731536824823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 53.129682191411696は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7253372180755755
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 123.80543558918298は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0927397124915794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 31.625373717674627は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5000356662807883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 570.8703768931241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7565375075615246
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.5563316273827628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1921021431657427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 136.9090609868282は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.13643219178891
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 94.6771858812517は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9762453407821097
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.041900276605545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7025942515450618
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.478146811744194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.81145078603413
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.163921881880055は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7898571260743815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.31687274251117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0135480736001197
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.00708745220221は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1463478401440277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.024563456664579は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6047187794508158
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.850791654978977は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0354614247141976
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.615716794116746は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7494051977945305
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 142.34104053292907は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1533301362559594
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 657.5721772756267は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.817943429362754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 177.25283744519876は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2485931960521666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.778778247479448は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2501218098608827
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 44.99712578680175は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6531847738909569
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 484.0623875934189は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6849013385895883
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 225.35557425471652は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.35286830497688
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.2946049889708675は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7989684816253141
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.10666174274879は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9088420520943146
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 437.3414758719678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.640820666204151
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 63.07528611325666は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.799859229179731
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 227.04972289876713は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3561209762056716
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.44848664309232は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.265960746131355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2977879765819116は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.11320374629960539
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 103.85126067988655は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0164117729269195
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 117.77678544660084は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.071059696682116
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.31294834984749は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.571859566957729
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.333193015447293は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3489508193479525
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 138.29695002348103は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1408126023610956
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.42417352212143は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1278875572519649
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 259.04635052765195は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4133774782797044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 639.7825393276796は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.806032383329965
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.660132605610988は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1024382546215823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 65.51960713221244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8163712846494349
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0406586903095523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.017308315274043085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 68.68453668737958は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.836858973053014
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 77.22494159870888は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8877575885388096
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.332289835166655は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5835647632427141
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.6166019876788384は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5583007166505031
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.238854180375226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9158668163400538
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 60.60493361104796は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.782507979823706
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 860.8920844157277は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9349487146591002
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.00891321823482は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6813218749200973
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 102.79558445035654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0119744600869796
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.041774920431781は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7025834535981869
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.311601320131368は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7252254701692991
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.1535269982628は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4175302650042192
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.081224665791645は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0035132933484647
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1976724141362993は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5048339703482794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 51.37025429596244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7107117155989704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9674638404551は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5985129772763172
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.667374110001276は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4093814406282372
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8563082110987688は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2686500857118427
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 334.0607185054096は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.523825410869166
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 443.9768415111748は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.647360317262793
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 700.0782010725045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8451465548676085
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.52164845752011は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6859355470140605
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1791572694564398は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.07157173274740447
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 45.891156914812576は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6617290063846966
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.7379733822834735は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5726362044883545
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 18.889179264804596は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2762130882283431
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.628930734624971は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0655397837395573
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 678.1463848173812は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8313234508823557
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.795294302272038は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7630754956244326
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 178.92255170489568は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2526650832377833
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.938777754967081は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6936194833465876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 25.27226271418508は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4026441275666028
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 95.48161114056306は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9799197386082055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 337.5481199419181は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5283356934206043
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.18142757432087は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3387407985307498
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 557.1218715692978は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7459502083883667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0593826805402156は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.025052868536053596
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 38.132128546708074は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5812910483968996
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.38771882323642は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6847351483365016
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.560154506038892は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.816914068084489
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.47740244560785は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0598436100841704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 69.35844293674332は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8410993348780336
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.76674612501838は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.42759557978464
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.231949321315641は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1532643885952507
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.817714142872678は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6828410277387011
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 80.38965890043255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.905200185921005
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 186.77056823008343は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.271308440082894
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.483846688236523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7390853047273215
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.382280572065862は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6417001794773549
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 224.28822051378438は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.350806465289614
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 670.801370715855は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8265939413725154
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 67.12153250787921は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8268618636745977
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.182391128531753は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9128802354780616
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 823.206159681754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9155086113969757
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 141.92378469937404は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1520551840275157
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.490084585898117は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.17321092220162138
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 297.38905409213265は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.47332497953607
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 100.09013983059782は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.000391295979999
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.121403352339754は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.32662325080843624
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.6491567594331404は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4231076577092757
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7323270256073537は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2386298807588213
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 296.7909782048625は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.472450695207409
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 46.41316053416911は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6666411429894743
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 83.45462443162829は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9214504070367489
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.47514002537624は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5247224023269454
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.065048387806489は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.314930232414281
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.195420250359373は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6227754701160326
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 110.76519941723758は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.044403333722295
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.545872606802456は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7439698892594837
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.32108017587887は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5946254396784139
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.993230946521619は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6013244281256004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.697262715212648は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.43092324908933255
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 57.271187281832084は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7579361865113277
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.020797429552356は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2309799030541853
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.16457818926156は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5206744780028234
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.22945249998558は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3469287663803566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 140.3674003098771は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1472662565868434
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.359145282611486は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5232149147534484
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 467.5669433969525は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6698437993080844
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.3779492926776595は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3762025894983666
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.089849819996694は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0449256649238805
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1327484277696303は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05413346806027419
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.289845520659017は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3598061846157269
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.77430162936975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9432125598294971
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 34.59604585131726は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5390264640214748
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.595996699544244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9342962400709183
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 128.00661129116307は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1072324006878835
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 28.097314422682548は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.448664811465662
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.02724311335683は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3429601451045061
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 253.6042699496762は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.404156561512419
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 74.75116308981102は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8736179544487366
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 331.5326394220446は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5205262911814934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 396.82886306470454は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5986032527307708
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 288.9921790957194は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.460886089740865
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 252.73426950628746は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.402664134078199
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 54.193865322913474は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.733950127734024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 985.854775770085は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9938129446300303
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 367.1405208391931は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5648323196870284
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.7788308055364743は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2501346418915008
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.48779116101196は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5248865026243617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 768.5454215708845は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.885669539701298
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.029876344900364は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0012955787773004
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6822522501687924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2258911178843045
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.2236188734277436は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3470603515469227
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3566360654723497は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13246335837800083
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.679577961298833は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3556349686166165
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 727.3968004602222は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8617713864278955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.46777310072783は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6071093062775255
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 131.70323906514864は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.119596455985492
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 370.66316492874597は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5689794296685355
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 40.620477605308075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6087450254235496
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 26.48195862586348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4229501027067704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4683480916046352は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1668290231159718
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 532.8708152971383は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7266219350983087
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 61.28217060616155は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7873341395485571
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 697.6235780865798は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.843621150335996
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 210.96452626898542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3242094347250646
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8014446451191217は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4473820454875702
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.681277854595136は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.42834182124315934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.878873739466099は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6883195791365175
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 338.0105654769099は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.5289302755930576
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 104.77491990252778は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.020257337500122
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.1616551562699042は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.3347864131722449
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.548518606545677は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2442404605079807
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 822.744988642809は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.915265245677559
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 61.526313946494255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7890608972000117
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.34932078960386は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.37094232186181086
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.434226209363507は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.128212656799596
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 240.33477480075348は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.380816614796448
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 578.1974435759945は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7620761671629106
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 268.0960783936925は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.428290461336718
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 119.30584447605314は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.0766617191232175
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9111498847480526は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.592304459488746
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.842628246582262は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5846283708636649
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 37.260712849219765は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5712511592967011
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.9699887959843814は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.598789281108449
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0604799040540924は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.31396838318917963
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.252863065933045は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5122657814000896
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 5.397702625100908は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7322089543525391
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 751.062207893258は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8756759096085602
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6813318398966428は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.22565343742111088
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.124719733138464は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0836717085313574
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.822997060766927は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.45071042597073474
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 35.67347312685752は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.552345393790295
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.235261741589486は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2364178831640333
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.061944455260294は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9572213958648087
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.35002663014401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.2866815670457126
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.806592081496035は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.25686010233716816
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 15.156111124468556は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.18058778085781
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 133.71005836729077は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1261640783846794
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.569366424632317は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.024048954522847
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.510092519529826は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8756452872669873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.891824450042553は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.46117192531271456
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.4358125657052256は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5360294636864872
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.836150776103873は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0348750392528208
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 671.9371370785241は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.827328644635754
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.828445885318188は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2620821114853972
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2265250334227407は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.08867641659981251
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 232.53459848133292は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.366487580071679
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.373597053141996は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0159293744657745
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 88.71037639287498は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9479744219354638
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 761.9282857875031は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.881914096598873
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 73.87334057787213は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8684877384109018
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3514290693026583は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.13079325638410055
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 664.1184905379669は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.822245572132857
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 176.89284030003049は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2477102552889514
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 48.04878395991781は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.6816824008249522
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.732917360399687は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9882430359126466
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 97.87271357466402は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9906616295384878
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 16.764086772145543は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.22437990010779
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 524.4030957549961は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7196652468344915
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.178565149215846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1198681278831728
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.756675367254473は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4735844070380697
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 321.19234583947906は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.506765187293799
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.156088473921074は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6186847841514377
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 14.962689569409646は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.175009665732062
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 660.1864356242586は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8196665969496806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 191.93491038944177は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.283153974269527
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 19.737963291907786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.295302336949609
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 59.480516528245275は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7743747312754823
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.406860339053974は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9246338326577948
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 150.25488002225887は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1768285860479653
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.8046919289547554は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.4478851647355867
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 173.3709120635005は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2389762339129504
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 43.349986891148255は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.636988970483444
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 710.8316992120966は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.8517667867274223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 583.1465133285874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7657776832943024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.012491934710846は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0418856033531934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.2730769238372295は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5149562122146526
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.980878131650563は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4768443490641316
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.2668735773541602は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1027332783428877
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 219.5573558793415は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3415479919495934
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 29.27110124088545は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.4664390618202987
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.217565593262328は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8583907394405218
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 104.8410177574807は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.020531228263807
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 250.52914733594466は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.398858260306132
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.95005281847812は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3607836893829617
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1407696663076903は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05719796453239323
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 76.3406174521459は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8827556682535747
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 413.36860844345307は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6163374928586833
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.671554607914226は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8242270451564035
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.0439414583669162は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.018676145197792704
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 143.383032892395は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1564977625090815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 412.7509915508752は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.615688125240843
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 400.01411757556184は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6020753190203876
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 8.879491356148401は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9483880888028325
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 316.4836947490475は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.50035134006293
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 11.903346446835982は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0756690739205041
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.200371694454786は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6232877231855543
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 91.27352008427967は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.960344799995454
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 535.1637082726164は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7284866544022375
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1590950769391186は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06411906124096223
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 496.8153072228734は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.696194968287714
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.909027618040762は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.037786041244656
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.52723415914872は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5968964264997125
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 278.18687292016523は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4443366326551526
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 286.1803835123863は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.4566398613444393
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.9669622019321207は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.29379601439313974
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.1340192749989315は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.05462043635100844
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 70.22293496310088は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.8464789768189112
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 538.3823366853308は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7310908030622643
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 365.0562457147378は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.562359783145913
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 17.133749592546092は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.233852415455563
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 325.3824529464709は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.512394128828261
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 165.0404707072325は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2175904536058013
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.366523402224075は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6401357920862806
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.208004775676244は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9641655358660124
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 152.4434536216014は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.1831087791962585
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.694709855610395は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.103622779290297
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 3.1764855782659596は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.5019468879118815
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.416739936689398は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6451018281952667
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 89.85828809072342は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.9535581404996694
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 421.1904631191822は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6244785290338566
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 62.68630894050398は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.7971726987117578
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 224.56922390253362は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3513502381002978
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.94604207748539は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.28915222638564997
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 399.6358066311874は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6016643932818373
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 20.755773354251126は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3171389197057044
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 891.6670682230088は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9502027272192644
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 986.6625541232237は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.9941686461447024
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 13.184101788173932は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1200505473469433
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 50.41275272349295は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.702540412176961
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 4.5694519418437345は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.6598641140947112
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.991647479918416は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8445795229750696
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 468.53801000848654は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.6707448286652915
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 6.283671880170465は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.7982134990363248
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.6438074567054728は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.21585094618001188
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.460520375745447は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1645076202017871
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.165852913793563は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.06664376246657955
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 176.78356194289614は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.2474418800809692
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.3443396017395897は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.12850899232730695
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.8582734147357636は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.2691096137346247
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 7.927109445881769は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.8991148543349906
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 12.965271883720542は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.1127816284221068
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 2.0194636408799975は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.30523603838873425
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 32.76101475965705は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5153573453989462
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 542.040134379969は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.7340314442772202
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 845.0136068243775は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.926863702229178
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 33.8604800682971は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5296931111720418
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 208.35778459971212は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 2.3188097310737943
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 22.531740386680703は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.3527947386008798
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 1.4845781987690854は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.1716030785905006
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 9.114559660989872は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 0.9597356920341471
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 10.180875360074761は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.0077851206044992
    },
    {
        "question": "問題文: 39.41580562075592は何桁ですか？",
        "answer": 1.5956704075467072
    }
]